author,updated_at,like_count,text,video_id,cleaned_text,sentiment,sentiment_score,keywords,entities,topic
@tod_bybein,2026-06-28T21:06:27Z,8,Watch all matches in 4K HDR  on TOD: https://tod.go.link/E7sV6,HW51rM36Ark,watch all matches in 4k hdr on tod,neutral,0.0,"['hdr tod', '4k hdr', 'matches 4k']",[],-1
@Mohamedoumimoun,2026-06-30T23:29:24Z,0,South Africa vs Afrique,HW51rM36Ark,south africa vs afrique,neutral,0.0,"['africa vs', 'south africa', 'vs afrique']","[('south africa', 'GPE')]",16
@Mohamedoumimoun,2026-06-30T23:27:46Z,0,Sud Afrique vs Afrique 😅,HW51rM36Ark,sud afrique vs afrique,neutral,0.0,"['sud afrique', 'afrique vs', 'vs afrique']",[],9
@Masta-m7k,2026-06-30T08:03:58Z,0,Canada,HW51rM36Ark,canada,neutral,0.0,[],"[('canada', 'GPE')]",124
@georgesmelki3319,2026-06-30T01:51:15Z,0,"Well done Canada, my grandsons' country ❤",HW51rM36Ark,well done canada my grandsons country,positive,0.2732,"['canada grandsons', 'grandsons country', 'canada']","[('canada', 'GPE')]",16
@N.roger3497,2026-06-30T00:18:26Z,0,😂😂 south Africans please come back first and fix your country 😂,HW51rM36Ark,south africans please come back first and fix your country,positive,0.3182,"['south africans', 'africans come', 'africans']",[],16
@Fizzlebells,2026-06-30T00:03:21Z,0,The token white guy saved the day lol,HW51rM36Ark,the token white guy saved the day laughing out loud,positive,0.7184,"['token white', 'day laughing', 'white guy']",[],104
@cryptolad-i1d,2026-06-29T19:53:22Z,0,Canada played better. Well deserved win,HW51rM36Ark,canada played better well deserved win,positive,0.8807,"['canada played', 'deserved win', 'better deserved']","[('canada', 'GPE')]",16
@Yeadris,2026-06-29T18:00:28Z,0,BAFANADA TIRAMISU,HW51rM36Ark,bafanada tiramisu,neutral,0.0,"['bafanada tiramisu', 'bafanada', 'tiramisu']","[('bafanada tiramisu', 'ORG')]",-1
@ZØVØ_155,2026-06-29T16:51:19Z,0,South Africa vs Canada? It seems to me Africa Vs Africa? Am I right or am I right?😂,HW51rM36Ark,south africa vs canada it seems to me africa vs africa am i right or am i right,neutral,0.0,"['africa vs', 'vs africa', 'africa right']","[('south africa', 'GPE'), ('canada', 'GPE'), ('africa', 'LOC')]",16
@FooVault,2026-06-29T16:13:28Z,1,Excellent defending by South Africa,HW51rM36Ark,excellent defending by south africa,positive,0.5719,"['defending south', 'excellent defending', 'defending']","[('south africa', 'GPE')]",16
@aatr01,2026-06-29T15:16:51Z,1,The of the most 50%-50% chance of winning game I've ever seen.,HW51rM36Ark,the of the most 50 50 chance of winning game i ve ever seen,positive,0.6872,"['50 chance', 'chance winning', '50 50']",[],-1
@AmethFall-r3x1z,2026-06-29T14:07:45Z,0,Je suis très content de vouloir éliminer Afrique du Sud Par ce que se qu'ils ont fait c'est tellement mal au cœur,HW51rM36Ark,je suis très content de vouloir éliminer afrique du sud par ce que se qu ils ont fait see est tellement mal au cœur,neutral,0.0,"['au cœur', 'par ce', 'est tellement']","[('cœur', 'ORG')]",39
@muhammedjuwara3633,2026-06-29T14:04:13Z,0,As an African i am very happy Canada eliminated South Africa. Thank you Canada 🇨🇦 ❤,HW51rM36Ark,as an african i am very happy canada eliminated south africa thank you canada,positive,0.7574,"['canada eliminated', 'happy canada', 'thank canada']","[('canada', 'GPE'), ('south africa', 'GPE'), ('canada', 'GPE')]",16
@AshrafBegum-q6b2s,2026-06-29T13:32:57Z,2,Unfortunately south Africa failed and got knocked out 😢😢 may allah help them qualify for the next world cup❤❤,HW51rM36Ark,unfortunately south africa failed and got knocked out may allah help them qualify for the next world cup,negative,-0.4588,"['africa failed', 'south africa', 'qualify world']","[('south africa', 'GPE')]",16
@yahkoobtkyahkoob3754,2026-06-29T12:45:31Z,0,South Africa Gud team but prob . Lake of strikers .,HW51rM36Ark,south africa good team but problem lake of strikers,negative,-0.5423,"['lake strikers', 'strikers', 'south africa']","[('south africa', 'GPE')]",16
@sofianekentouri4001,2026-06-29T12:05:39Z,0,Le commentateur sportif en dirait c'est fait avec l'AI🤣🤣,HW51rM36Ark,le commentateur sportif en dirait see est fait avec l Artificial Intelligence,positive,0.7269,"['sportif en', 'commentateur sportif', 'le commentateur']","[('dirait', 'GPE'), ('l artificial intelligence', 'ORG')]",39
@MwakaAli-f4e,2026-06-29T12:02:18Z,0,I'm not happy because of Canada why not score even 10 goals,HW51rM36Ark,i am not happy because of canada why not score even 10 goals,negative,-0.4585,"['canada score', 'happy canada', '10 goals']","[('canada', 'GPE')]",16
@Peacelily01,2026-06-29T10:53:35Z,1,"Me looking for Cruz and steak😂
👇🏼",HW51rM36Ark,me looking for cruz and steak,neutral,0.0,"['cruz steak', 'looking cruz', 'cruz']",[],-1
@AyanmixDbarista,2026-06-29T09:23:17Z,0,"Bayana bayana eye go first blur…..


Thanks Canada 😂😂😂😂",HW51rM36Ark,bayana bayana eye go first blur thanks canada,positive,0.4404,"['bayana eye', 'bayana bayana', 'bayana']","[('bayana bayana eye go', 'PERSON'), ('canada', 'GPE')]",16
@blerimkamberaj1398,2026-06-29T08:41:44Z,0,South Africa one of the most crap teams of the World Cup😂,HW51rM36Ark,south africa one of the most crap teams of the world cup,negative,-0.4391,"['south africa', 'africa crap', 'africa']","[('south africa', 'GPE')]",16
@Shahbuddin123Chowdhury,2026-06-29T08:35:03Z,0,কানাডা  ❤❤❤,HW51rM36Ark,ক ন ড,neutral,0.0,[],[],83
@syedahamed3724,2026-06-29T07:54:59Z,1,Good 👍 ( Indian from Dubai),HW51rM36Ark,good indian from dubai,positive,0.4404,"['indian dubai', 'good indian', 'dubai']","[('dubai', 'GPE')]",115
@EM-jp9ig,2026-06-29T07:10:32Z,0,GO BECK,HW51rM36Ark,go beck,neutral,0.0,[],[],-1
@EM-jp9ig,2026-06-29T07:07:55Z,0,GO BECK HOME AND FIX YOUR KONTRY,HW51rM36Ark,go beck home and fix your kontry,neutral,0.0,"['beck home', 'beck', 'fix kontry']",[],-1
@hammacheamir6704,2026-06-29T07:07:32Z,0,"I loooove goals going on like that one ! Well done, Canada",HW51rM36Ark,i loooove goals going on like that one well done canada,positive,0.5574,"['loooove goals', 'goals going', 'goals']","[('canada', 'GPE')]",16
@cedcol356,2026-06-29T06:43:36Z,0,Goodbye and good riddance,HW51rM36Ark,goodbye and good riddance,positive,0.4404,"['goodbye', 'goodbye good', 'good riddance']",[],34
@youfe7731,2026-06-29T06:13:57Z,0,FIFA the corrupted produced some laugh worthy 32 round games like this one while a strong team like Morocco will face another strong team like Holland 😂😂😂 Enjoy it Canada as long as it lasts ....Farmer league level worthy was this game 😂😂😂,HW51rM36Ark,fifa the corrupted produced some laugh worthy 32 round games like this one while a strong team like morocco will face another strong team like holland enjoy it canada as long as it lasts farmer league level worthy was this game,positive,0.9769,"['fifa corrupted', 'fifa', 'holland enjoy']","[('fifa', 'ORG'), ('morocco', 'GPE'), ('holland', 'GPE'), ('canada', 'GPE')]",16
@Ezekieltanu-t2s,2026-06-29T06:06:36Z,1,They should go to keep their jobs😂,HW51rM36Ark,they should go to keep their jobs,neutral,0.0,['jobs'],[],-1
@ssemujjuvincentwilliam7569,2026-06-29T05:33:32Z,0,"Well done Canada, one welcome foreigners, another mistreated them. God and time",HW51rM36Ark,well done canada one welcome foreigners another mistreated them god and time,positive,0.7351,"['canada welcome', 'foreigners mistreated', 'welcome foreigners']","[('canada', 'GPE')]",16
@GeorgeWilliam-h2z,2026-06-29T05:26:46Z,0,Canada have taken bafana bafana job 😂😂😂😂,HW51rM36Ark,canada have taken bafana bafana job,neutral,0.0,"['bafana job', 'bafana bafana', 'bafana']","[('canada', 'GPE')]",16
@jean-francoisdepondicherry9626,2026-06-29T05:15:04Z,0,The poorest technical level i have ever seen on a world cup... A shame ! And SA that refuse to play for minutes.. 😢,HW51rM36Ark,the poorest technical level i have ever seen on a world cup a shame and sa that refuse to play for minutes,negative,-0.7506,"['shame sa', 'sa refuse', 'poorest technical']",[],-1
@LewismutwiriMiriti-d9y,2026-06-29T05:11:11Z,0,From 🇰🇪 congratulation canada for mauling xenophobia fc😂😂😂😂😂😂😂🤸🏻🤸🏼‍♂️🤸🏼‍♂️🤸🏼‍♂️🤸🏼‍♂️🤸🏻.,HW51rM36Ark,from congratulation canada for mauling xenophobia fruit cake,positive,0.5994,"['xenophobia fruit', 'mauling xenophobia', 'canada mauling']","[('congratulation canada', 'ORG')]",16
@PurnaGurung-uq5tg,2026-06-29T04:45:31Z,1,I see the pressure of knockout round😮,HW51rM36Ark,i see the pressure of knockout round,negative,-0.296,"['pressure knockout', 'knockout round', 'knockout']",[],-1
@ReactionTv-l7s,2026-06-29T04:41:54Z,1,I love Portugal and Brazil 🇧🇷❤️‍🩹💥💥,HW51rM36Ark,i love portugal and brazil,positive,0.6369,"['love portugal', 'portugal brazil', 'portugal']","[('portugal', 'GPE'), ('brazil', 'GPE')]",-1
@theodoremwamburi3410,2026-06-29T04:35:55Z,1,It was a hard fought win for Canada.Kudos Canada 💪💪💪,HW51rM36Ark,it was a hard fought win for canada kudos canada,positive,0.6597,"['win canada', 'canada kudos', 'kudos canada']","[('canada', 'GPE'), ('canada', 'GPE')]",16
@Concerned36,2026-06-29T04:24:38Z,1,Just Africans playing against each other,HW51rM36Ark,just africans playing against each other,positive,0.2023,"['africans playing', 'just africans', 'africans']",[],16
@brahimdaoui1611,2026-06-29T04:17:06Z,0,"Je  félicite le Canada pour sa qualification au 8ème de finale.
Les sud africains à vos valises, dégagez et passez voir Ben Battouch.",HW51rM36Ark,je félicite le canada pour sa qualification au 8ème de finale les sud africains à vos valises dégagez et passez voir ben battouch,neutral,0.0,"['sud africains', 'pour sa', 'africains vos']","[('félicite le canada', 'ORG')]",39
@perminuskamau9999,2026-06-29T04:14:18Z,2,Congratulations to Canada 🎉🇰🇪,HW51rM36Ark,congratulations to canada,positive,0.5994,"['congratulations canada', 'congratulations', 'canada']","[('canada', 'GPE')]",16
@Lema-MA,2026-06-29T04:11:40Z,1,"Africa Stand UP and rejoice, against the coloniser sympathisers.",HW51rM36Ark,africa stand up and rejoice against the coloniser sympathisers,positive,0.4404,"['africa stand', 'africa', 'coloniser sympathisers']","[('africa', 'LOC')]",16
@ikeforson4034,2026-06-29T03:58:22Z,0,"Am very happy today since I was born. 
Canada 🇨🇦 1 - Animals of South Africa 🇿🇦 0",HW51rM36Ark,am very happy today since i was born canada 1 animals of south africa 0,positive,0.6115,"['canada animals', 'born canada', 'happy today']","[('canada', 'GPE'), ('south africa', 'GPE')]",16
@petermomanyi6368,2026-06-29T03:44:05Z,0,Finally  they are going home to look after their business😂,HW51rM36Ark,finally they are going home to look after their business,neutral,0.0,"['look business', 'going home', 'home look']",[],-1
@Mahmud-m7q,2026-06-29T03:42:31Z,2,Canada has played well from the start. They deserved the victory❤,HW51rM36Ark,canada has played well from the start they deserved the victory,positive,0.5423,"['canada played', 'deserved victory', 'start deserved']","[('canada', 'GPE')]",16
@oxxo902,2026-06-29T03:35:44Z,1,South Africa did well but wasn’t lucky enough to avoid this goal.,HW51rM36Ark,south africa did well but wasn t lucky enough to avoid this goal,positive,0.3506,"['south africa', 'africa did', 'avoid goal']","[('south africa', 'GPE')]",16
@ronrob578,2026-06-29T03:12:04Z,0,Canada 👍👍👍👍👍,HW51rM36Ark,canada,neutral,0.0,[],"[('canada', 'GPE')]",124
@peterirungumwangi,2026-06-29T03:01:59Z,1,It's funny 😅 this time this players are playing very good in last time,HW51rM36Ark,it s funny this time this players are playing very good in last time,positive,0.7841,"['playing good', 'players playing', 'time players']",[],-1
@aklilushiferawgebre795,2026-06-29T02:55:43Z,0,Go homes try to stops xenophobia.  Inshalla see you next world cup  no deserved  lost.,HW51rM36Ark,go homes try to stops xenophobia inshalla see you next world cup no deserved lost,negative,-0.2115,"['xenophobia inshalla', 'stops xenophobia', 'xenophobia']",[],-1
@sidhuofficial942,2026-06-29T02:39:43Z,0,Congratulations Canada from India Punjab❤,HW51rM36Ark,congratulations canada from india punjab,positive,0.5994,"['congratulations canada', 'canada india', 'punjab']","[('congratulations canada', 'ORG'), ('india', 'GPE')]",16
@freetorv3sta155,2026-06-29T02:31:05Z,2,No SA. Not like that..😢 Fought hard just to concede a goal at stoppage time life is truly unfair,HW51rM36Ark,no sa not like that fought hard just to concede a goal at stoppage time life is truly unfair,negative,-0.4493,"['concede goal', 'truly unfair', 'unfair']",[],106
@jazzyhIGH,2026-06-29T02:15:09Z,0,Literally ur best Africans vs my best Africans 😂🤤,HW51rM36Ark,literally your best africans vs my best africans,positive,0.8555,"['best africans', 'africans vs', 'africans']",[],-1
@karimmbarki,2026-06-29T01:51:47Z,1,Frogs to the swamps..,HW51rM36Ark,frogs to the swamps,neutral,0.0,"['frogs swamps', 'frogs', 'swamps']",[],-1
@karimmbarki,2026-06-29T01:50:43Z,1,Go Canada.. You are the best..,HW51rM36Ark,go canada you are the best,positive,0.6369,"['canada best', 'canada', 'best']","[('canada', 'GPE')]",16
@KingsleyNwanya-g3f,2026-06-29T01:46:10Z,0,Go beck 😂,HW51rM36Ark,go beck,neutral,0.0,[],[],-1
@liadiabiodun6981,2026-06-29T01:45:13Z,1,GOOOO BEEEECK TO YAA COUNTRY😂😂😂😂😂😂😂😂😂😂😂😂😂,HW51rM36Ark,goooo beeeeck to yaa country,neutral,0.0,"['yaa country', 'beeeeck yaa', 'goooo beeeeck']","[('yaa', 'ORG')]",79
@HakimovitchHD,2026-06-29T01:25:35Z,2,"Congratulations to Canada, greetings from Morocco.",HW51rM36Ark,congratulations to canada greetings from morocco,positive,0.7717,"['canada greetings', 'greetings morocco', 'congratulations canada']","[('canada', 'GPE'), ('morocco', 'GPE')]",16
@tariqal-basha5719,2026-06-29T01:16:14Z,0,please a shorter highlight of 90 seconds,HW51rM36Ark,please a shorter highlight of 90 seconds,positive,0.5719,"['shorter highlight', '90 seconds', 'highlight 90']",[],27
@baselabdelfattah9394,2026-06-29T01:13:52Z,0,"So sad to see south africa lose 
All love from Egypt",HW51rM36Ark,so sad to see south africa lose all love from egypt,negative,-0.2247,"['love egypt', 'africa lose', 'south africa']","[('south africa', 'GPE'), ('egypt', 'GPE')]",16
@sh230968,2026-06-29T00:38:13Z,1,RSA deserved to win.,HW51rM36Ark,rsa deserved to win,positive,0.5859,"['rsa deserved', 'deserved win', 'rsa']","[('rsa', 'PERSON')]",89
@anouarben3056,2026-06-29T00:34:25Z,0,❤🇨🇦,HW51rM36Ark,,neutral,0.0,[],[],0
@KarimBegriche-y9y,2026-06-29T00:01:52Z,6,"Sad to see South Africa eliminated. Hard luck. Greetings from Algeria.
 🇩🇿❤🇿🇦",HW51rM36Ark,sad to see south africa eliminated hard luck greetings from algeria,positive,0.3182,"['greetings algeria', 'algeria', 'africa eliminated']","[('south africa', 'GPE'), ('algeria', 'GPE')]",16
@hasnainarnob6479,2026-06-28T23:45:13Z,4,"Well played South Africa.
Congratulations Canada.",HW51rM36Ark,well played south africa congratulations canada,positive,0.8126,"['congratulations canada', 'africa congratulations', 'south africa']","[('south africa congratulations', 'ORG'), ('canada', 'GPE')]",16
@MariaMaria-jr8cc,2026-06-28T23:33:38Z,0,Boring match.......congratulations to Canada 🇨🇦,HW51rM36Ark,boring match congratulations to canada,positive,0.3818,"['boring match', 'congratulations canada', 'match congratulations']","[('boring match congratulations', 'ORG'), ('canada', 'GPE')]",16
@AghNaaShaWorld,2026-06-28T23:24:23Z,1,"Bad luck SA, better luck next time",HW51rM36Ark,bad luck sa better luck next time,positive,0.6597,"['luck sa', 'bad luck', 'luck time']",[],-1
@syrian-weeb,2026-06-28T22:53:13Z,0,"جنوب افريقيا رفعوا ضغطي 

اداء رهيب من الحارس وانقاذ من الدفاع 
بس التمريرات كلها غير دقيقة واستحواذ ضعيف، ب سيناريو تاني كان ممكن تخلص 3 صفر ل كندا",HW51rM36Ark,جنوب افريقيا رفعوا ضغطي اداء رهيب من الحارس وانقاذ من الدفاع بس التمريرات كلها غير دقيقة واستحواذ ضعيف ب سيناريو تاني كان ممكن تخلص 3 صفر ل كندا,neutral,0.0,"['رفعوا ضغطي', 'افريقيا رفعوا', 'التمريرات كلها']","[('رفعوا ضغطي', 'ORG'), ('التمريرات كلها غير دقيقة واستحواذ', 'PERSON')]",9
@nandssharon9030,2026-06-28T22:52:19Z,0,It's was African team vs African team 😂😂😂 I saw Canadian team with the same type of hair like mine 🤭🤨🤨🤨,HW51rM36Ark,it s was african team vs african team i saw canadian team with the same type of hair like mine,positive,0.3612,"['african team', 'canadian team', 'vs african']",[],16
@EdwardKenway007,2026-06-28T22:48:47Z,0,ودي يا كندي 😂,HW51rM36Ark,ودي يا كندي,neutral,0.0,"['يا كندي', 'كندي', 'ودي يا']","[('ودي يا كندي', 'ORG')]",9
@ArtHeights-s2d3b,2026-06-28T22:43:53Z,2,"So happy, south Africa go 🏡,  congratulations Canada 🎉",HW51rM36Ark,so happy south africa go congratulations canada,positive,0.8357,"['congratulations canada', 'africa congratulations', 'south africa']","[('south africa', 'GPE'), ('congratulations canada', 'ORG')]",16
@sguitirahmed1375,2026-06-28T22:30:51Z,3,"من المغرب 🇲🇦 
هنيئا لأبناء عمتي الكنديين 😁التأهيل😂",HW51rM36Ark,من المغرب هنيئا لأبناء عمتي الكنديين التأهيل,neutral,0.0,"['المغرب هنيئا', 'الكنديين التأهيل', 'هنيئا لأبناء']","[('من المغرب هنيئا لأبناء عمتي الكنديين', 'PERSON')]",9
@فتحيعزالدين-ج4ض,2026-06-28T22:28:40Z,3,Team Canada was a team from the African continent,HW51rM36Ark,team canada was a team from the african continent,neutral,0.0,"['canada team', 'team canada', 'team african']","[('team canada', 'ORG')]",16
@yogendralamtarimagar4195,2026-06-28T22:28:35Z,3,Congratulation Canada I'm watching from Nepal🇳🇵🇳🇵,HW51rM36Ark,congratulation canada i am watching from nepal,positive,0.5994,"['congratulation canada', 'watching nepal', 'canada watching']","[('congratulation canada', 'ORG')]",16
@LanacondaMortel-x1b,2026-06-28T22:23:08Z,1,Grosse grosse félicitations  tout les Canadiens pour leur calif de la part du MAGESTIEUX et  AUTHENTIQUE LION DE L'ATLAS.❤❤❤,HW51rM36Ark,grosse grosse félicitations tout les canadiens pour leur calif de la part du magestieux et authentique lion de l atlas,positive,0.3612,"['magestieux et', 'les canadiens', 'du magestieux']","[('calif de la', 'ORG'), ('magestieux', 'ORG'), ('lion de l', 'ORG')]",39
@melodicanime5412,2026-06-28T22:22:43Z,1,Football stands for unity not xénophobia,HW51rM36Ark,football stands for unity not xénophobia,neutral,0.0,"['unity xénophobia', 'xénophobia', 'football stands']",[],10
@juzsean,2026-06-28T22:21:45Z,0,9:22 Indian 😂,HW51rM36Ark,9 22 indian,neutral,0.0,"['22 indian', 'indian', '22']",[],-1
@bassenecyrille4348,2026-06-28T22:20:32Z,0,Congratulation Canada,HW51rM36Ark,congratulation canada,positive,0.5994,"['congratulation canada', 'congratulation', 'canada']","[('congratulation canada', 'ORG')]",16
@Akrambinnoor.001,2026-06-28T22:15:50Z,1,অসাধারণ কানাডা,HW51rM36Ark,অস ধ রণ ক ন ড,neutral,0.0,"['অস রণ', 'অস', 'রণ']",[],83
@Hussinalashpat,2026-06-28T22:15:10Z,11,"Bafana Bafana should not worry, only one team will win the trophy, the rest will join them",HW51rM36Ark,bafana bafana should not worry only one team will win the trophy the rest will join them,positive,0.8129,"['bafana worry', 'bafana bafana', 'bafana']","[('bafana bafana', 'PERSON')]",-1
@mymarr-w4y,2026-06-28T22:09:38Z,1,congratulation canada from morocco,HW51rM36Ark,congratulation canada from morocco,positive,0.5994,"['congratulation canada', 'canada morocco', 'morocco']","[('congratulation canada', 'ORG'), ('morocco', 'GPE')]",16
@gogotammihack,2026-06-28T22:02:52Z,0,Black players in Canada will do anything to get citizenship,HW51rM36Ark,black players in canada will do anything to get citizenship,neutral,0.0,"['canada citizenship', 'players canada', 'black players']","[('canada', 'GPE')]",16
@القرآن_العظيم-ب9ه,2026-06-28T22:02:47Z,0,"*ثقِل بِها موازينـك*📿 : 

سُبحان الله ، الحمدلله ، لا إله إلا الله 
الله أكبُر ، لا حول ولا قوة إلا بالله",HW51rM36Ark,ثق ل ب ها موازينـك س بحان الله الحمدلله لا إله إلا الله الله أكب ر لا حول ولا قوة إلا بالله,neutral,0.0,"['موازينـك بحان', 'بحان الله', 'ثق ها']","[('موازينـك', 'PERSON')]",9
@ZenZanoman,2026-06-28T21:56:28Z,0,Canada will meet Morocco in ⅛ after having beaten Netherlands,HW51rM36Ark,canada will meet morocco in ⅛ after having beaten netherlands,negative,-0.4215,"['meet morocco', 'canada meet', 'morocco']","[('canada', 'GPE'), ('morocco', 'GPE'), ('⅛', 'GPE'), ('netherlands', 'GPE')]",16
@perfectcell1157,2026-06-28T21:52:20Z,1,Very good game from both sides,HW51rM36Ark,very good game from both sides,positive,0.4927,"['game sides', 'good game', 'sides']",[],46
@MuhammadYasir-q4h,2026-06-28T21:50:36Z,2,"Congratulations 🎊 to Canada 
Well played South Africa",HW51rM36Ark,congratulations to canada well played south africa,positive,0.8126,"['congratulations canada', 'canada played', 'south africa']","[('canada', 'GPE'), ('south africa', 'GPE')]",16
@anahowa7605,2026-06-28T21:49:33Z,1,Congratulations Canada. They were the best. Love from Morocco ❤❤❤,HW51rM36Ark,congratulations canada they were the best love from morocco,positive,0.9231,"['love morocco', 'congratulations canada', 'canada best']","[('canada', 'GPE'), ('morocco', 'GPE')]",16
@Crazyfootballchallengesindia,2026-06-28T21:45:57Z,2,Hard luck south Africa 🫶 and congratulations to Canada,HW51rM36Ark,hard luck south africa and congratulations to canada,positive,0.7579,"['africa congratulations', 'congratulations canada', 'south africa']","[('south africa', 'GPE'), ('canada', 'GPE')]",16
@Issa-f6v5j,2026-06-28T21:40:35Z,5,"The Knesset decides to execute Palestinian prisoners in a wicked criminal move. Do not stay silent; spread the word now!
#SavePalestinianPrisoners",HW51rM36Ark,the knesset decides to execute palestinian prisoners in a wicked criminal move do not stay silent spread the word now savepalestinianprisoners,negative,-0.8779,"['execute palestinian', 'palestinian prisoners', 'knesset decides']",[],9
@PrinceHalamadrid,2026-06-28T21:40:31Z,35,"If the Tunisia  is not in a hurry, they can wait for South Africa  so they can both go home together. 😗😗🇹🇳🇿🇦",HW51rM36Ark,if the tunisia is not in a hurry they can wait for south africa so they can both go home together,neutral,0.0,"['tunisia hurry', 'tunisia', 'south africa']","[('south africa', 'GPE')]",16
@EmmanuelNti-e5s,2026-06-28T21:37:46Z,0,Go berk and fix your country 😂😂😂,HW51rM36Ark,go berk and fix your country,neutral,0.0,"['berk fix', 'fix country', 'berk']",[],124
@Sammy_M_M,2026-06-28T21:37:17Z,8,So happy for my Canada,HW51rM36Ark,so happy for my canada,positive,0.6115,"['happy canada', 'canada', 'happy']","[('canada', 'GPE')]",16
@paradiseparadise9312,2026-06-28T21:34:50Z,2,"Thanks GOD, CANADIAN justice has triumphed over South Africa racism",HW51rM36Ark,thanks god canadian justice has triumphed over south africa racism,positive,0.7579,"['canadian justice', 'africa racism', 'justice triumphed']","[('south africa', 'GPE')]",16
@Aw.369,2026-06-28T21:31:26Z,0,"The calm nature of the Canadians outperformed the enthusiasm of the Bafana Bafana team🙂
The level of the two teams is somewhat close, I think the Canadian team will also leave the tournament in the next match, the storm is coming, this calmness cannot deal with it.

Generally, the two teams played well.
Blessings to the two teams.. and congratulations to Canada",HW51rM36Ark,the calm nature of the canadians outperformed the enthusiasm of the bafana bafana team the level of the two teams is somewhat close i think the canadian team will also leave the tournament in the next match the storm is coming this calmness cannot deal with it generally the two teams played well blessings to the two teams and congratulations to canada,positive,0.9585,"['canadian team', 'canadians outperformed', 'bafana team']","[('canada', 'GPE')]",16
@xuxushushu,2026-06-28T21:26:39Z,10,Congratulations Canada! 🇨🇦❤️,HW51rM36Ark,congratulations canada,positive,0.5994,"['congratulations canada', 'congratulations', 'canada']","[('canada', 'GPE')]",16
@abdulsalam563,2026-06-28T21:26:36Z,0,Elimination for banana bafana۔۔۔۔۔I am a supporter of African nations,HW51rM36Ark,elimination for banana bafana i am a supporter of african nations,positive,0.2732,"['banana bafana', 'bafana supporter', 'elimination banana']",[],16
@AnisAbdelkader-s3k,2026-06-28T21:25:34Z,0,خطئ بدائي. ممنوع منعا باتا إخراج الكرة من طرف المدافع إلى وسط الميدان . من المفروض إخراجها للجانبين. او إخراجها بقوة لكي تصل لوسط الميدان وتبعد الخطر. حظ موفق للبافانا بافانا,HW51rM36Ark,خطئ بدائي ممنوع منعا باتا إخراج الكرة من طرف المدافع إلى وسط الميدان من المفروض إخراجها للجانبين او إخراجها بقوة لكي تصل لوسط الميدان وتبعد الخطر حظ موفق للبافانا بافانا,neutral,0.0,"['خطئ بدائي', 'الميدان وتبعد', 'وسط الميدان']","[('منعا', 'PERSON'), ('الكرة من', 'PERSON'), ('لوسط الميدان وتبعد الخطر', 'PERSON')]",9
@ZarwatMouhamed,2026-06-28T21:25:09Z,2,منتخب كندا ضعيف وجنوب أفريقيا أضعف,HW51rM36Ark,منتخب كندا ضعيف وجنوب أفريقيا أضعف,neutral,0.0,"['كندا ضعيف', 'منتخب كندا', 'أفريقيا أضعف']","[('منتخب كندا ضعيف وجنوب', 'ORG')]",9
@mominurrahman4806,2026-06-28T21:24:59Z,32,"Congratulations Canada 🎉

But also South Africa played very very well today ❤",HW51rM36Ark,congratulations canada but also south africa played very very well today,positive,0.8425,"['africa played', 'congratulations canada', 'south africa']","[('congratulations canada but', 'ORG'), ('south africa', 'GPE')]",16
@mardigabajian4509,2026-06-28T21:24:53Z,0,Thanks,HW51rM36Ark,thanks,positive,0.4404,[],[],19
@UarBlack-jl5kt,2026-06-28T21:23:47Z,2,Boring match,HW51rM36Ark,boring match,negative,-0.3182,"['boring match', 'boring', 'match']",[],18
@BB-2000,2026-06-28T21:23:33Z,0,Oh Canada!,HW51rM36Ark,oh canada,neutral,0.0,[],"[('canada', 'GPE')]",124
@السيديوسف-خ3م,2026-06-28T21:22:33Z,3,كندا طول الماتش بتهاجم,HW51rM36Ark,كندا طول الماتش بتهاجم,neutral,0.0,"['كندا طول', 'الماتش بتهاجم', 'كندا']","[('كندا طول', 'PERSON')]",9
@Adamnajdi1994,2026-06-28T21:20:01Z,0,Davies played like garbage,HW51rM36Ark,davies played like garbage,positive,0.5994,"['davies played', 'davies', 'garbage']",[],-1
@Mosa-Shahein,2026-06-28T21:17:44Z,1,*I have watched it live and both of these teams got what they deserved.*,HW51rM36Ark,i have watched it live and both of these teams got what they deserved,neutral,0.0,"['watched live', 'got deserved', 'deserved']",[],-1
@MahoudWalied-m1o,2026-06-28T21:16:33Z,2,مباراة موملة جدا انا قفلت التلفزيون من غير ما النتيجة 😂😂,HW51rM36Ark,مباراة موملة جدا انا قفلت التلفزيون من غير ما النتيجة,neutral,0.0,"['قفلت التلفزيون', 'التلفزيون من', 'ما النتيجة']","[('موملة جدا', 'PERSON')]",9
@Aw.369,2026-06-28T21:15:27Z,13,"بما ان عدد الدول المشاركة  اصبح اكبر فدوري المجموعات  يمكن ان نعتبره مجرد ملحق للتاهل لكاس العالم 
كاس العالم يبدأ الان",HW51rM36Ark,بما ان عدد الدول المشاركة اصبح اكبر فدوري المجموعات يمكن ان نعتبره مجرد ملحق للتاهل لكاس العالم كاس العالم يبدأ الان,neutral,0.0,"['الدول المشاركة', 'المجموعات يمكن', 'فدوري المجموعات']","[('بما', 'PERSON'), ('نعتبره', 'ORG'), ('العالم كاس العالم يبدأ', 'ORG'), ('الان', 'ORG')]",9
@nodysol3283,2026-06-28T21:15:12Z,1,حاى كندا تقوز لان اصل اللاعبين افارقة كل منتخبات اوروبا القوية اللاعبين من اصول افريقية 😂😂😂😂,HW51rM36Ark,حاى كندا تقوز لان اصل اللاعبين افارقة كل منتخبات اوروبا القوية اللاعبين من اصول افريقية,neutral,0.0,"['كندا تقوز', 'اللاعبين افارقة', 'افارقة كل']","[('حاى كندا', 'ORG'), ('لان اصل اللاعبين افارقة', 'PERSON'), ('القوية اللاعبين من اصول', 'PERSON')]",9
@i.m.khXn913,2026-06-28T21:15:02Z,0,91st minute goal was so crazyyyyyyyyyyyyyyy 💯💯🥴,HW51rM36Ark,91st minute goal was so crazyyyyyyyyyyyyyyy,neutral,0.0,"['goal crazyyyyyyyyyyyyyyy', 'minute goal', '91st minute']",[],17
@nodysol3283,2026-06-28T21:13:52Z,0,👎👎👎👎👎👎👎👎👎👎👎👎👎👎👎👎👎👎,HW51rM36Ark,,neutral,0.0,[],[],0
@nodysol3283,2026-06-28T21:13:31Z,0,"جنوب افريقيا من تستحق الفوز 
مافي زي المعلقين العرب الاجانب تحسهم يتكلموا مو يعلقوا 

والله مافي اجمل من مونديال قطر سواء الملاعب وكل شي",HW51rM36Ark,جنوب افريقيا من تستحق الفوز مافي زي المعلقين العرب الاجانب تحسهم يتكلموا مو يعلقوا والله مافي اجمل من مونديال قطر سواء الملاعب وكل شي,neutral,0.0,"['زي المعلقين', 'تستحق الفوز', 'مافي زي']","[('تستحق الفوز', 'GPE'), ('العرب الاجانب', 'PERSON'), ('والله مافي اجمل من', 'PERSON')]",9
@hamidhmoda5541,2026-06-28T21:13:20Z,0,ها وحد لعدو مشا لعقوبة لكراغلة,HW51rM36Ark,ها وحد لعدو مشا لعقوبة لكراغلة,neutral,0.0,"['مشا لعقوبة', 'لعدو مشا', 'لعقوبة لكراغلة']","[('وحد لعدو مشا لعقوبة', 'ORG')]",9
@LeelammaAntony-i5h,2026-06-28T21:12:22Z,5,6 mins is crazy,HW51rM36Ark,6 minutes is crazy,negative,-0.34,"['minutes crazy', 'minutes', 'crazy']",[],-1
@KohlerSAStudios,2026-06-28T21:10:37Z,3,08:46 Goal 🥅 ⚽️ for Canada 🇨🇦,HW51rM36Ark,08 46 goal for canada,neutral,0.0,"['46 goal', 'goal canada', '08 46']","[('canada', 'GPE')]",17
@littujibin137,2026-06-28T21:10:37Z,1,Polli,HW51rM36Ark,polli,neutral,0.0,[],[],103
@Ahm3d-Rabby,2026-06-28T21:08:17Z,0,1st,HW51rM36Ark,1st,neutral,0.0,[],[],14
@johnkkm,2026-06-28T21:07:28Z,1,❤❤,HW51rM36Ark,,neutral,0.0,[],[],0
@vyshakhpp4061,2026-06-28T21:07:26Z,0,❤,HW51rM36Ark,,neutral,0.0,[],[],0
@tod_bybein,2026-06-28T21:06:27Z,8,Watch all matches in 4K HDR  on TOD: https://tod.go.link/E7sV6,HW51rM36Ark,watch all matches in 4k hdr on tod,neutral,0.0,"['hdr tod', '4k hdr', 'matches 4k']",[],-1
@eren_yagami7034,2026-07-03T13:02:33Z,1,Jordan's Gk 😂,M6mpXtMm93M,jordan s gk,neutral,0.0,"['jordan gk', 'jordan', 'gk']","[('jordan s', 'PERSON')]",57
@FatehaNipu,2026-07-03T12:48:18Z,0,🇧🇩,M6mpXtMm93M,,neutral,0.0,[],[],0
@bencio22,2026-07-03T11:23:25Z,1,"Two free kicks in the so-called ""keepers corner"", the one that isn't covered by the wall. Weird stuff.",M6mpXtMm93M,two free sneakers in the so called keepers corner the one that isn t covered by the wall weird stuff,positive,0.3818,"['free sneakers', 'sneakers called', 'sneakers']",[],-1
@Lone_AE,2026-07-03T11:09:56Z,3,1:39  blud disnt even try 😭✌,M6mpXtMm93M,1 39 blud disnt even try,neutral,0.0,"['39 blud', 'blud disnt', 'blud']",[],49
@malimmikael9501,2026-07-03T08:44:51Z,0,jordan cant event beat messi...no debate Lebron is the GOAT,M6mpXtMm93M,jordan cant event beat messi no debate lebron is the goat,negative,-0.296,"['debate lebron', 'messi debate', 'lebron goat']","[('jordan', 'PERSON'), ('lebron', 'PERSON')]",52
@SereneGhibliLiving,2026-07-03T08:14:10Z,0,3mt,M6mpXtMm93M,3mt,neutral,0.0,[],[],14
@CarolineNaisarian,2026-07-03T08:10:30Z,0,Argentina!!!!!!!,M6mpXtMm93M,argentina,neutral,0.0,[],"[('argentina', 'GPE')]",53
@bijuab7644,2026-07-03T07:57:50Z,0,Messi free kick G. O. A. T ❤❤❤,M6mpXtMm93M,messi free kick g Oh a t,positive,0.5106,"['messi free', 'messi', 'free kick']","[('messi free kick', 'PERSON')]",65
@bijuab7644,2026-07-03T07:54:29Z,0,Vamos Messi vamos Argentina G. O. A. T ❤️❤️❤️🇦🇷🇦🇷🇦🇷🇦🇷,M6mpXtMm93M,vamos messi vamos argentina g Oh a t,neutral,0.0,"['vamos argentina', 'vamos messi', 'messi vamos']","[('vamos messi vamos', 'PERSON')]",116
@Fatima-f5w1z,2026-07-03T07:28:16Z,0,Lodabesmessi ❤❤❤,M6mpXtMm93M,lodabesmessi,neutral,0.0,['lodabesmessi'],"[('lodabesmessi', 'PERSON')]",-1
@x1910Polaroid,2026-07-03T07:06:05Z,0,Argentina with the easiest group and round of 32/16/quarter-finals to the semi-finals for sure,M6mpXtMm93M,argentina with the easiest group and round of 32 16 quarter finals to the semi finals for sure,positive,0.6249,"['argentina easiest', 'argentina', 'semi finals']","[('argentina', 'GPE'), ('the easiest group', 'ORG')]",53
@NaveenSharma.7520,2026-07-03T06:38:28Z,0,❤❤,M6mpXtMm93M,,neutral,0.0,[],[],0
@RAYMund188,2026-07-03T06:03:58Z,0,"Messi 🐐 
Ronaldo 🥇",M6mpXtMm93M,messi ronaldo,neutral,0.0,"['messi ronaldo', 'ronaldo', 'messi']","[('messi', 'PERSON')]",144
@jasururinboyev-m1i,2026-07-03T02:45:09Z,1,darvozabon kuchsiz va zaif,M6mpXtMm93M,darvozabon kuchsiz va zaif,neutral,0.0,"['darvozabon kuchsiz', 'darvozabon', 'va zaif']","[('kuchsiz va zaif', 'PERSON')]",-1
@duranarts,2026-07-02T21:15:40Z,0,They seriously left that HUGE GAP for Messi?! Someone explain this to me please...,M6mpXtMm93M,they seriously left that huge gap for messi someone explain this to me please,positive,0.4404,"['gap messi', 'messi explain', 'messi']","[('messi', 'PERSON')]",3
@PablinDeDios777,2026-07-02T20:30:57Z,0,Golazo que metio Leo en los ultimos minutos,M6mpXtMm93M,golazo que metio leo en los ultimos minutos,neutral,0.0,"['ultimos minutos', 'golazo que', 'que metio']","[('leo en', 'PERSON'), ('los ultimos', 'GPE')]",4
@edwaldocamargo4387,2026-07-02T19:15:51Z,0,Está acontecendo uma situação muito feia nessa copa FIFA de futebol Messi tem marcado os seus gols com a ajuda do time adversário todos os gols de Messi foram feitos sem nenhuma marcação contra Messi isso é muito feio é preciso que o futebol da copa FIFA seja um futebol sem política para um jogar para o outro time vencer o futebol é maravilhoso por que tem disputa de futebol e jogo não deve ter política na copa FIFA de futebol mais infelizmente o mundo vê muita política na copa FIFA de futebol e isso é muito feio de assistir,M6mpXtMm93M,está acontecendo uma situação muito feia nessa copa fifa de futebol messi tem marcado operating system seus gols com a ajuda do time adversário todos operating system gols de messi foram feitos sem nenhuma marcação contra messi isso é muito feio é preciso que Oh futebol the copa fifa seja um futebol sem política para um jogar para Oh outro time vencer Oh futebol é maravilhoso por que tem disputa de futebol e jogo não deve ter política not applicable copa fifa de futebol mais infelizmente Oh mundo vê muita política not applicable copa fifa de futebol e isso é muito feio de assistir,neutral,0.0,"['futebol isso', 'futebol copa', 'futebol mais']","[('muito feia', 'PERSON'), ('nessa', 'ORG'), ('fifa de futebol', 'ORG'), ('messi', 'PERSON'), ('de messi', 'PERSON'), ('messi', 'PERSON'), ('muito feio', 'PERSON'), ('jogar para', 'PERSON'), ('jogo', 'GPE'), ('muito feio de assistir', 'PERSON')]",-1
@ThePodiumG,2026-07-02T18:50:56Z,0,🔥🔥,M6mpXtMm93M,,neutral,0.0,[],[],0
@Tomioka_giyu999,2026-07-02T17:14:40Z,0,0:13 bro didn't even tried😢,M6mpXtMm93M,0 13 brother didn t even tried,neutral,0.0,"['13 brother', 'brother didn', '13']","[('didn', 'PERSON')]",-1
@ArmourWanniang,2026-07-02T17:02:34Z,0,Who is he????,M6mpXtMm93M,who is he,neutral,0.0,[],[],64
@regulardad85,2026-07-02T16:49:20Z,0,"Where's the clip of Valentin Barco going in for a reckless tackle, injuring the jordanian guy and somehow drawing a free kick for Argentina. That was embarassing.",M6mpXtMm93M,where s the clip of valentin barco going in for a reckless tackle injuring the jordanian guy and somehow drawing a free kick for argentina that was embarassing,positive,0.1531,"['clip valentin', 'argentina embarassing', 'valentin barco']","[('valentin barco', 'ORG'), ('argentina', 'GPE')]",-1
@SkAltab-q6u8s,2026-07-02T16:41:17Z,0,This tutorial is top notch I really appreciate the effort.,M6mpXtMm93M,this tutorial is top notch i really appreciate the effort,positive,0.5849,"['tutorial', 'tutorial notch', 'really appreciate']",[],111
@adrenalinejunkie5644,2026-07-02T15:31:06Z,0,Why Argentina is wearing this dress??,M6mpXtMm93M,why argentina is wearing this dress,neutral,0.0,"['argentina wearing', 'wearing dress', 'argentina']","[('argentina', 'GPE')]",53
@patriceklemenko6782,2026-07-02T14:16:57Z,0,"Les vacances de l'argentine sont bientôt finies, ils vont devoir disputer un très dur 16 '...
La ficelle est vraiment grosse Messi....😂😂",M6mpXtMm93M,les vacances de l argentine sont bientôt finies ils vont devoir disputer un très dur 16 la ficelle est vraiment grosse messi,positive,0.4588,"['argentine sont', 'vacances argentine', 'ficelle est']","[('de l', 'ORG'), ('un', 'ORG')]",-1
@Sportmanship_09,2026-07-02T12:56:23Z,1,Goal number six 🎉,M6mpXtMm93M,goal number six,positive,0.0772,"['goal number', 'goal', 'number']",[],17
@JacobWalson-x1c,2026-07-02T12:14:36Z,0,The content is really helpful I will come back to watch it again.,M6mpXtMm93M,the content is really helpful i will come back to watch it again,positive,0.4754,"['content really', 'content', 'helpful']",[],-1
@FrankVie-b8t,2026-07-02T10:01:02Z,0,Insane goals ❤️,M6mpXtMm93M,insane goals,negative,-0.4019,"['insane goals', 'goals', 'insane']",[],17
@Lsytia,2026-07-02T09:59:27Z,0,Maybe the keeper is waiting the moment messi hit his goal and let it in. It was history for him and he will remembered it for a long time,M6mpXtMm93M,maybe the keeper is waiting the moment messi hit his goal and let it in it was history for him and he will remembered it for a long time,neutral,0.0,"['messi hit', 'messi', 'moment messi']",[],65
@Tharsika-o5g,2026-07-02T09:51:34Z,0,This video is top notch It helped me understand better.,M6mpXtMm93M,this video is top notch it helped me understand better,positive,0.5719,"['helped understand', 'understand better', 'notch helped']",[],55
@ThomasReichelt-j5s,2026-07-02T09:39:22Z,0,❤ 6,M6mpXtMm93M,6,neutral,0.0,[],[],14
@MuktadirTousif,2026-07-02T09:31:38Z,1,Please upload all matches,M6mpXtMm93M,please upload all matches,positive,0.3182,"['upload matches', 'upload', 'matches']",[],-1
@HindlalChauhan1,2026-07-02T07:34:00Z,1,The production quality is very impressive It deserves more views.,M6mpXtMm93M,the production quality is very impressive it deserves more views,positive,0.5563,"['production quality', 'quality impressive', 'quality']",[],92
@vaioletesorrengail,2026-07-02T05:26:13Z,0,"ставил на мелгейме на аргентину с кф 5.8 4к р, так что топ матч",M6mpXtMm93M,ставил на мелгейме на аргентину с кф 5 8 4к р так что топ матч,neutral,0.0,"['аргентину кф', 'кф 4к', 'топ матч']","[('ставил на', 'PERSON')]",2
@KoKo-e7e3i,2026-07-02T05:10:20Z,0,🇦🇷🇦🇷🇦🇷🇦🇷🇦🇷🇦🇷🇦🇷🇦🇷🇦🇷🇦🇷🇦🇷🇦🇷🇦🇷🇦🇷🇦🇷🇦🇷🇦🇷❤❤❤❤❤❤❤❤❤,M6mpXtMm93M,,neutral,0.0,[],[],0
@Iyhooreitfos8,2026-07-02T04:28:06Z,0,I hope Argentina wins the wc and beat France..love,M6mpXtMm93M,i hope argentina wins the who cares and beat france love,positive,0.93,"['hope argentina', 'argentina wins', 'beat france']","[('argentina', 'GPE'), ('france', 'GPE')]",136
@AshWickramasinghe,2026-07-02T03:29:57Z,0,"He walks in, he scores...🎉",M6mpXtMm93M,he walks in he scores,neutral,0.0,"['walks scores', 'scores', 'walks']",[],-1
@SumonAhmed-w9d,2026-07-02T03:29:19Z,0,All Bangladeshi arzentina sapurtar love form Bangladesh 🇧🇩🇦🇷,M6mpXtMm93M,all bangladeshi arzentina sapurtar love form bangladesh,positive,0.6369,"['bangladeshi arzentina', 'form bangladesh', 'bangladeshi']",[],87
@srinivasaraoalugolu9153,2026-07-02T02:42:31Z,0,The editing is well made This deserves recognition.,M6mpXtMm93M,the editing is well made this deserves recognition,positive,0.2732,"['editing deserves', 'deserves recognition', 'deserves']",[],110
@jhayrdedase,2026-07-02T01:53:46Z,0,FIRE!!,M6mpXtMm93M,fire,negative,-0.34,[],[],-1
@FriedaScheepers-y9d,2026-07-02T01:30:10Z,0,I have no words other than “Go Messi” 👏🏻👏🏻🎉🎉,M6mpXtMm93M,i have no words other than go messi,negative,-0.296,"['words messi', 'messi', 'words']","[('messi', 'PERSON')]",3
@altairlavin7834,2026-07-02T01:21:10Z,1,Cuando argentina jugará contra un equipo de verdad ??,M6mpXtMm93M,cuando argentina jugará contra un equipo de verdad,neutral,0.0,"['cuando argentina', 'argentina jugará', 'equipo verdad']","[('cuando argentina jugará', 'PERSON'), ('contra', 'ORG'), ('un', 'ORG')]",4
@srlee1739,2026-07-02T00:43:44Z,0,역시는 역시. 메시는 메시.,M6mpXtMm93M,역시는 역시 메시는 메시,neutral,0.0,"['역시 메시는', '역시는 역시', '메시는 메시']",[],22
@SamirDiwan-b4d,2026-07-01T22:48:51Z,1,This channel is exactly what I needed I will definitely recommend this.,M6mpXtMm93M,this channel is exactly what i needed i will definitely recommend this,positive,0.6369,"['channel', 'channel exactly', 'definitely recommend']",[],69
@Cptidris,2026-07-01T22:39:31Z,0,Keeper had no reflexes at all,M6mpXtMm93M,keeper had no reflexes at all,negative,-0.296,"['keeper reflexes', 'reflexes', 'keeper']",[],32
@M4RCUS333,2026-07-01T22:02:11Z,0,"your watching this video, not commenting on this video. Well explained",M6mpXtMm93M,your watching this video not commenting on this video well explained,positive,0.2732,"['video commenting', 'commenting video', 'video explained']",[],-1
@AnthonyLopez-h8f,2026-07-01T18:56:12Z,0,🐐🐐🐐,M6mpXtMm93M,,neutral,0.0,[],[],0
@babaratandevsewasocietymarhana,2026-07-01T17:39:08Z,0,Who is your best player,M6mpXtMm93M,who is your best player,positive,0.6369,"['best player', 'player', 'best']",[],68
@NVH2411,2026-07-01T17:04:11Z,0,G.O.A.T,M6mpXtMm93M,g Oh a t,neutral,0.0,[],[],64
@shivaguru2475,2026-07-01T16:41:54Z,0,Jordan scored one goal in each game. That was a decent debut with other 3 teams being strong. Hope they come back next time with more power 😊❤,M6mpXtMm93M,jordan scored one goal in each game that was a decent debut with other 3 teams being strong hope they come back next time with more power,positive,0.7351,"['jordan scored', 'scored goal', 'jordan']","[('jordan', 'GPE')]",57
@jaheem8599,2026-07-01T16:38:10Z,0,best goalkeeper hhhhhh,M6mpXtMm93M,best goalkeeper hhhhhh,positive,0.6369,"['best goalkeeper', 'goalkeeper hhhhhh', 'goalkeeper']",[],32
@tofoo72,2026-07-01T16:20:42Z,0,At least show the entirety of Jordan’s goal 😂 😂,M6mpXtMm93M,at least show the entirety of jordan s goal,neutral,0.0,"['jordan goal', 'entirety jordan', 'jordan']","[('jordan', 'GPE')]",57
@KongkaKynjing-s8f,2026-07-01T15:30:43Z,0,Argentina 🇦🇷 🏅🏆👑💛💚🍍🍹🍎🍈🌽🍑,M6mpXtMm93M,argentina,neutral,0.0,[],"[('argentina', 'GPE')]",53
@SskefayaJoarder,2026-07-01T15:26:20Z,0,🤚,M6mpXtMm93M,,neutral,0.0,[],[],0
@NafeesbegumNafeesbegum-el5tx,2026-07-01T15:24:45Z,0,"Very well done, appreciate this video!",M6mpXtMm93M,very well done appreciate this video,positive,0.6549,"['appreciate video', 'appreciate', 'video']",[],-1
@MohammadNoman-s4m,2026-07-01T14:20:08Z,0,"This was very informative, appreciate it.",M6mpXtMm93M,this was very informative appreciate it,positive,0.4549,"['informative appreciate', 'informative', 'appreciate']",[],-1
@standfortruth8576,2026-07-01T11:51:54Z,0,Messi in..... Messi goal!😆,M6mpXtMm93M,messi in messi goal,neutral,0.0,"['messi goal', 'messi', 'messi messi']","[('messi', 'PERSON'), ('messi', 'GPE')]",3
@Jbakt1189,2026-07-01T11:49:32Z,0,Leo Messi king of the world,M6mpXtMm93M,leo messi king of the world,neutral,0.0,"['leo messi', 'messi king', 'messi']","[('leo messi', 'PERSON')]",-1
@AmAhmad-q8b,2026-07-01T11:19:54Z,1,"أنا اسفه ع الاكلام قبيح 😂 
Jordan really should have beaten Argentina. The proof is that the referees themselves admitted after the match that the scoreline should have been 2–1 in Jordan's favor; it felt like the match was fixed or rigged. The referee was incredibly biased—he ignored clear goals and a penalty for Jordan, while Argentina's goals came from fake dives. Jordan’s goal was spectacular—a strike the likes of which hadn't been seen since 1966, involving 14 accurate passes. We lost, but it was a loss caused by cheating—you guys cheated, Argentina. Still, we are proud of Jordan. Thank you, *Nashama*! Greetings from Jordan. 🫡🇯🇴❣️",M6mpXtMm93M,أنا اسفه ع الاكلام قبيح jordan really should have beaten argentina the proof is that the referees themselves admitted after the match that the scoreline should have been 2 1 in jordan s favor it felt like the match was fixed or rigged the referee was incredibly biased he ignored clear goals and a penalty for jordan while argentina s goals came from fake dives jordan s goal was spectacular a strike the likes of which hadn t been seen since 1966 involving 14 accurate passes we lost but it was a loss caused by cheating you guys cheated argentina still we are proud of jordan thank you nashama greetings from jordan,negative,-0.7105,"['cheated argentina', 'beaten argentina', 'argentina proof']","[('jordan', 'GPE'), ('jordan', 'GPE'), ('jordan', 'GPE'), ('argentina s', 'PERSON'), ('jordan', 'GPE'), ('jordan', 'GPE'), ('jordan', 'GPE')]",-1
@mrrazaofficial1769,2026-07-01T10:59:21Z,0,Second GOAT for a reason 🙌🏻,M6mpXtMm93M,second goat for a reason,neutral,0.0,"['second goat', 'goat reason', 'goat']",[],44
@achmadsofyan-f8t,2026-07-01T10:37:07Z,0,Lawan nya negara negara enteng,M6mpXtMm93M,lawan nya negara negara enteng,neutral,0.0,"['negara enteng', 'negara negara', 'nya negara']","[('lawan nya', 'PERSON'), ('negara', 'GPE')]",11
@nivedaya6663,2026-07-01T10:31:18Z,0,𝗠𝗲𝘀𝘀𝗶😂😂❤❤❤❤❤❤❤❤❤❤❤❤❤𝗺𝘆 𝗳𝗮𝘃𝗿𝗲𝘁 𝗽𝗹𝗮𝘆𝗮𝗿𝗲 𝗶𝘀 𝗺𝗲𝘀𝘀𝗶,M6mpXtMm93M,𝗠𝗲𝘀𝘀𝗶 𝗺𝘆 𝗳𝗮𝘃𝗿𝗲𝘁 𝗽𝗹𝗮𝘆𝗮𝗿𝗲 𝗶𝘀 𝗺𝗲𝘀𝘀𝗶,neutral,0.0,"['𝗽𝗹𝗮𝘆𝗮𝗿𝗲 𝗶𝘀', '𝗺𝘆 𝗳𝗮𝘃𝗿𝗲𝘁', '𝗶𝘀 𝗺𝗲𝘀𝘀𝗶']",[],127
@sprazini3014,2026-07-01T10:30:53Z,0,"Lionel Messi 🐐 

July 1, 2026",M6mpXtMm93M,lionel messi july 1 2026,neutral,0.0,"['messi july', 'lionel messi', 'july 2026']","[('lionel messi', 'PERSON')]",-1
@IsraelCavallo-e7r,2026-07-01T09:48:07Z,0,Messi keeps breaking new records,M6mpXtMm93M,messi keeps breaking new records,neutral,0.0,"['messi keeps', 'messi', 'new records']","[('messi', 'PERSON')]",3
@MartinLunardini,2026-07-01T08:51:52Z,0,El arquero de Jordania tiene tatuado a messi en los glúteos,M6mpXtMm93M,el arquero de jordania tiene tatuado a messi en los glúteos,neutral,0.0,"['arquero jordania', 'jordania tiene', 'los glúteos']","[('el arquero de jordania', 'ORG'), ('tiene tatuado', 'PERSON'), ('los glúteos', 'GPE')]",4
@DreamBig-gs5,2026-07-01T08:33:54Z,4,Is match highlights duration 2:10 mandatory? 🤔,M6mpXtMm93M,is match highlights duration 2 10 mandatory,positive,0.0772,"['highlights duration', 'match highlights', 'highlights']",[],27
@mohanvishwakarma1225,2026-07-01T08:21:25Z,0,What a penalty’s 22 🛡️👑🧬❤️‍🩹🌍⚙️🙏🏻⚡️,M6mpXtMm93M,what a penalty s 22,negative,-0.4588,"['penalty 22', 'penalty', '22']",[],93
@mohanvishwakarma1225,2026-07-01T08:20:20Z,0,What A goal Boss 🧿⚡️❤️‍🩹🌍🛡️🧬👑🙏🏻⚙️,M6mpXtMm93M,what a goal boss,neutral,0.0,"['goal boss', 'goal', 'boss']",[],17
@AzimjonKonolov,2026-07-01T08:11:49Z,0,Messi is the goat,M6mpXtMm93M,messi is the goat,neutral,0.0,"['messi goat', 'messi', 'goat']","[('messi', 'PERSON')]",52
@rajeshpaul5029,2026-07-01T07:28:10Z,1,India ko vi chance do FIFA,M6mpXtMm93M,india knock out vi chance do fifa,positive,0.25,"['india knock', 'chance fifa', 'fifa']","[('india', 'GPE'), ('fifa', 'ORG')]",-1
@EmiJay-u5m,2026-07-01T07:04:25Z,0,The goalkeeper just did,M6mpXtMm93M,the goalkeeper just did,neutral,0.0,"['goalkeeper just', 'goalkeeper', 'just did']",[],32
@hiran1993,2026-07-01T07:00:30Z,0,Freekicks and penalties 😂,M6mpXtMm93M,freekicks and penalties,neutral,0.0,"['freekicks penalties', 'freekicks', 'penalties']",[],-1
@lolilurker,2026-07-01T06:05:10Z,1,Messi freekick n keeper watching 😂,M6mpXtMm93M,messi freekick and keeper watching,neutral,0.0,"['messi freekick', 'freekick keeper', 'keeper watching']","[('messi freekick', 'PERSON')]",65
@psgultrasss,2026-07-01T05:17:50Z,3,VAMOS ARGENTINA 🇦🇷VAMOS MESSI 🇦🇷,M6mpXtMm93M,vamos argentina vamos messi,neutral,0.0,"['vamos messi', 'vamos argentina', 'argentina vamos']","[('vamos argentina vamos messi', 'PERSON')]",116
@RanjitSardar-q7g,2026-07-01T05:10:08Z,0,🇧🇷🇧🇷🇧🇷🇧🇷🇧🇷🇧🇷🇧🇷🇧🇷🇧🇷🇧🇷🇧🇷🇧🇷🇧🇷🇧🇷🇧🇷🇧🇷🇧🇷🇧🇷🇧🇷🇧🇷🇧🇷🇧🇷👿👿👿👿👿👿👿,M6mpXtMm93M,,neutral,0.0,[],[],0
@HesbulhasanRuhan,2026-07-01T04:41:30Z,0,🇦🇷🇦🇷🇦🇷🇦🇷🇦🇷🇦🇷🇦🇷🇦🇷👑👑👑🏍️🏍️🏍️🏍️🍓🍓🍓🍓🍓🍓🌹🌹🌹🌹⛹️⛹️⛹️⛹️⛹️⛹️😜😶‍🌫️😜😜😜😜😜😜😜😜😜😜♥️♥️♥️♥️♥️♥️♥️♥️👍👍👍👍👍👍👍,M6mpXtMm93M,,neutral,0.0,[],[],0
@YashwantSuntyan-x6l,2026-07-01T03:37:42Z,0,Argentina’s win against Jordan in both teams’ final group stage game of the 2026 FIFA World Cup👍🙏🙏,M6mpXtMm93M,argentina s win against jordan in both teams final group stage game of the 2026 fifa world cup,positive,0.5859,"['argentina win', 'argentina', 'teams final']","[('argentina s', 'PERSON'), ('jordan', 'GPE')]",53
@Boringvllogs,2026-07-01T03:05:11Z,0,I’m the GOAT,M6mpXtMm93M,i am the goat,neutral,0.0,['goat'],[],21
@3licheikhLebatt,2026-07-01T03:04:41Z,0,❤,M6mpXtMm93M,,neutral,0.0,[],[],0
@Mohitkumar-i6p8u,2026-07-01T02:16:46Z,0,This tutorial is worth sharing I will definitely recommend this.,M6mpXtMm93M,this tutorial is worth sharing i will definitely recommend this,positive,0.836,"['tutorial', 'tutorial worth', 'definitely recommend']",[],111
@Sathish-f8h6t,2026-07-01T02:15:54Z,0,The idea is outstanding I enjoyed every second of it.,M6mpXtMm93M,the idea is outstanding i enjoyed every second of it,positive,0.8074,"['idea outstanding', 'outstanding enjoyed', 'enjoyed second']",[],51
@AchmadMujahid-p3v,2026-07-01T01:50:51Z,0,Messi 🎉🎉🎉,M6mpXtMm93M,messi,neutral,0.0,[],"[('messi', 'PERSON')]",3
@EddyMishima,2026-07-01T01:27:20Z,1,"1:07

Is the difference between Portugal and Argentina 

Ronaldo makes that Run ..they are afraid to risk that through ball ...for some unknown reasons.
Probably jealousy I guess.",M6mpXtMm93M,1 07 is the difference between portugal and argentina ronaldo makes that run they are afraid to risk that through ball for some unknown reasons probably jealousy i guess,negative,-0.5267,"['07 difference', 'difference portugal', 'ronaldo']","[('portugal', 'GPE'), ('argentina', 'GPE')]",33
@GavvlamahenderGavvla,2026-07-01T01:02:31Z,0,This channel is exactly what I needed This deserves recognition.,M6mpXtMm93M,this channel is exactly what i needed this deserves recognition,neutral,0.0,"['deserves recognition', 'needed deserves', 'channel exactly']",[],69
@ThaiTriniQueen,2026-07-01T00:39:15Z,0,"Puede que sea una mujer tailandesa-trinitense, pero mi sangre es blanca y celeste. 🇹🇭🇹🇹❤️🇦🇷",M6mpXtMm93M,puede que sea una mujer tailandesa trinitense pero mi sangre es blanca why celeste,neutral,0.0,"['blanca celeste', 'es blanca', 'que sea']",[],4
@PlvsVltra-ji3rs,2026-07-01T00:17:51Z,0,"Take note this is why Argentina keep winning, it's not just talent, but also IT'S 100% ARGENTINA BORN SQUAD. VAMOS MUCHACHOS",M6mpXtMm93M,take note this is why argentina keep winning it s not just talent but also it s 100 argentina born squad vamos muchachos,positive,0.1366,"['100 argentina', 'argentina born', 'note argentina']","[('argentina', 'GPE'), ('squad vamos muchachos', 'PERSON')]",53
@Tarikakamkhueang,2026-06-30T23:36:18Z,0,สุดยอดขริงๆเชียร์อาเจนแมสซี่,M6mpXtMm93M,ส ดยอดขร งๆเช ยร อาเจนแมสซ,neutral,0.0,"['งๆเช ยร', 'ยร อาเจนแมสซ', 'ยร']","[('ส ดยอดขร งๆเช ยร อาเจนแมสซ', 'PERSON')]",83
@GaneshTudu-r8s,2026-06-30T23:34:08Z,0,This channel is outstanding I really appreciate the effort.,M6mpXtMm93M,this channel is outstanding i really appreciate the effort,positive,0.7902,"['channel outstanding', 'really appreciate', 'appreciate effort']",[],69
@ivanhoesanchez2606,2026-06-30T22:13:48Z,0,Argentina llegó la perfección con 9 pts.,M6mpXtMm93M,argentina llegó la perfección con 9 pts,neutral,0.0,"['la perfección', 'argentina llegó', 'llegó la']","[('argentina llegó la perfección con', 'ORG')]",4
@ShivaRan-p4j,2026-06-30T22:00:16Z,0,Anulo Mufa,M6mpXtMm93M,anulo mufa,neutral,0.0,"['anulo mufa', 'anulo', 'mufa']","[('anulo mufa', 'PERSON')]",-1
@unronodd,2026-06-30T20:42:39Z,1,パルコだかバルコだかがタックルした謎ファウル(相手のファウル扱い)のときだけ全然リプレイなかったのがもうお察し,M6mpXtMm93M,パルコだかバルコだかがタックルした謎ファウル 相手のファウル扱い のときだけ全然リプレイなかったのがもうお察し,neutral,0.0,"['相手のファウル扱い のときだけ全然リプレイなかったのがもうお察し', 'パルコだかバルコだかがタックルした謎ファウル 相手のファウル扱い', 'パルコだかバルコだかがタックルした謎ファウル']",[],1
@SurajKumar-k9h3t,2026-06-30T20:39:29Z,0,The production quality is well made I learned a lot from it.,M6mpXtMm93M,the production quality is well made i learned a lot from it,positive,0.2732,"['production quality', 'quality learned', 'quality']",[],92
@ArnabMaity-tu6zd,2026-06-30T20:20:25Z,0,The idea is really helpful I learned a lot from it.,M6mpXtMm93M,the idea is really helpful i learned a lot from it,positive,0.4754,"['helpful learned', 'really helpful', 'idea']",[],51
@ColorTherapyLoop,2026-06-30T19:21:28Z,1,"If we judged countries by colors alone, Argentina would be near the top of my list. 🎨 🇦🇷",M6mpXtMm93M,if we judged countries by colors alone argentina would be near the top of my list,negative,-0.0516,"['colors argentina', 'countries colors', 'judged countries']","[('argentina', 'GPE')]",-1
@bendabuzzkill47,2026-06-30T18:43:55Z,1,"Goalie is paid, no doubt",M6mpXtMm93M,goalie is paid no doubt,positive,0.2755,"['goalie paid', 'goalie', 'paid doubt']",[],32
@Khunkhasi971,2026-06-30T18:21:35Z,0,Argentina without Di Maria can't win any cup.,M6mpXtMm93M,argentina without di maria can t win any cup,positive,0.5859,"['maria win', 'argentina di', 'di maria']","[('argentina', 'GPE')]",53
@HighGoalsTV,2026-06-30T18:10:12Z,0,Forca Messi!!!!!,M6mpXtMm93M,forca messi,neutral,0.0,"['forca messi', 'messi', 'forca']","[('forca messi', 'PERSON')]",3
@FitZap99,2026-06-30T18:03:42Z,0,MESSI GOAT 🐐🐐 MESSI GOAT 🐐🐐 MESSI GOAT 🐐🐐 MESSI GOAT 🐐🐐MESSI GOAT 🐐🐐 MESSI GOAT 🐐🐐MESSI GOAT 🐐🐐MESSI GOAT 🐐🐐 MESSI GOAT 🐐🐐 MESSI GOAT 🐐🐐 MESSI GOAT 🐐🐐MESSI GOAT 🐐🐐 MESSI GOAT,M6mpXtMm93M,messi goat messi goat messi goat messi goat messi goat messi goat messi goat messi goat messi goat messi goat messi goat messi goat messi goat,neutral,0.0,"['goat messi', 'messi goat', 'messi']","[('messi goat messi', 'PERSON'), ('messi goat messi', 'PERSON'), ('messi goat messi', 'PERSON'), ('messi goat messi', 'PERSON'), ('messi goat messi', 'PERSON'), ('messi goat messi', 'PERSON'), ('messi goat', 'PERSON')]",58
@sujon80751,2026-06-30T18:03:08Z,0,Leo you beauty of football 🐐💝,M6mpXtMm93M,leo you beauty of football,positive,0.5859,"['leo beauty', 'leo', 'beauty football']","[('leo', 'PERSON')]",-1
@sujon80751,2026-06-30T18:01:07Z,0,Vamos Argentina ❤,M6mpXtMm93M,vamos argentina,neutral,0.0,"['vamos argentina', 'vamos', 'argentina']","[('vamos argentina', 'PERSON')]",116
@JesicaBenitez-u6j,2026-06-30T17:57:22Z,0,🇦🇷🇦🇷,M6mpXtMm93M,,neutral,0.0,[],[],0
@memorablemoments001,2026-06-30T17:28:05Z,1,"2022 : Pressure Messi
2026 : Without Pressure Messi",M6mpXtMm93M,2022 pressure messi 2026 without pressure messi,negative,-0.0803,"['pressure messi', 'messi 2026', '2026 pressure']","[('messi', 'PERSON')]",3
@memorablemoments001,2026-06-30T17:27:00Z,6,Messi ageing like fine wine 🍷 ⚽️,M6mpXtMm93M,messi ageing like fine wine,positive,0.5106,"['messi ageing', 'messi', 'ageing like']","[('messi', 'PERSON')]",3
@Masti-d5k,2026-06-30T17:25:36Z,0,Defence 😂so ...,M6mpXtMm93M,defence so,positive,0.1027,['defence'],[],-1
@lostinthelaw,2026-06-30T17:15:18Z,0,Commentators:,M6mpXtMm93M,commentators,neutral,0.0,['commentators'],[],29
@thanachartkowapradit7950,2026-06-30T17:09:40Z,1,"I’m a Messi fan, but how could the goalkeeper fail to save that free kick? 😂",M6mpXtMm93M,i am a messi fan but how could the goalkeeper fail to save that free kick,positive,0.6858,"['goalkeeper fail', 'messi', 'messi fan']",[],65
@rinoyrinoyks822,2026-06-30T17:05:39Z,1,He is a real Goat Messi,M6mpXtMm93M,he is a real goat messi,neutral,0.0,"['goat messi', 'messi', 'real goat']",[],52
@shashankgorakh9510,2026-06-30T16:39:22Z,1,I think jordan need a new goalkeeper... He just don't even respond twice.,M6mpXtMm93M,i think jordan need a new goalkeeper he just denial of normal t even respond twice,neutral,0.0,"['jordan need', 'new goalkeeper', 'goalkeeper just']","[('jordan', 'PERSON')]",57
@mandarinconmigo,2026-06-30T16:24:46Z,0,Messi 🫶🏼,M6mpXtMm93M,messi,neutral,0.0,[],"[('messi', 'PERSON')]",3
@muhamadnaqiuddinsuhaimi8878,2026-06-30T16:22:47Z,2,Did Messi bribe the keeper? 😂😂😂,M6mpXtMm93M,did messi bribe the keeper,negative,-0.2023,"['messi bribe', 'did messi', 'bribe keeper']","[('messi', 'PERSON')]",65
@AlutaJohnMugwe,2026-06-30T16:14:16Z,0,Lautaro and messi are great,M6mpXtMm93M,lautaro and messi are great,positive,0.6249,"['lautaro messi', 'messi great', 'messi']","[('messi', 'PERSON')]",3
@satisfyingshortsclips5530,2026-06-30T16:13:57Z,0,Just when they givr and say ok hes the goat he goes and says camera bobo freekicko?,M6mpXtMm93M,just when they givr and say okay hes the goat he goes and says camera bobo freekicko,positive,0.2263,"['bobo freekicko', 'camera bobo', 'givr say']",[],40
@aneckumar5701,2026-06-30T15:42:39Z,1,"0:34 he is playing his regular game only the other person is doing his stunt with his head, how come it's a penalty when he didn't hit on his intentionally nor is his mistake. Other's guys unconventional play costed him the penalty.",M6mpXtMm93M,0 34 he is playing his regular game only the other person is doing his stunt with his head how come it s a penalty when he didn t hit on his intentionally nor is his mistake other s guys unconventional play costed him the penalty,negative,-0.1935,"['penalty', 'penalty didn', 'come penalty']",[],93
@utpalpaul9005,2026-06-30T15:16:00Z,0,Ronaldo ❤❤❤❤❤❤❤❤❤❤❤❤❤❤❤❤❤❤❤❤❤❤❤❤❤❤❤❤❤❤❤❤❤❤❤❤❤❤❤❤❤❤❤❤❤❤❤❤❤❤❤❤❤❤❤❤❤❤❤❤❤❤❤❤❤❤❤❤❤❤❤❤❤❤❤❤❤❤❤,M6mpXtMm93M,ronaldo,neutral,0.0,[],[],13
@Stryker-V37,2026-06-30T15:01:07Z,1,Jordan's goalkeeper for Manchester City! 🔵⚪,M6mpXtMm93M,jordan s goalkeeper for manchester city,neutral,0.0,"['jordan goalkeeper', 'goalkeeper manchester', 'goalkeeper']","[('jordan s goalkeeper', 'PERSON'), ('manchester city', 'GPE')]",57
@nerswnbty5568,2026-06-30T14:59:28Z,0,Messi G.O.A.T ❤❤❤❤❤,M6mpXtMm93M,messi g Oh a t,neutral,0.0,"['messi oh', 'messi', 'oh']","[('messi g', 'PERSON')]",3
@SudarsanSahoo-e7x6f,2026-06-30T14:58:47Z,0,The production quality is very impressive I will definitely recommend this.,M6mpXtMm93M,the production quality is very impressive i will definitely recommend this,positive,0.8313,"['production quality', 'quality impressive', 'quality']",[],92
@asankaindeewariud9745,2026-06-30T14:48:50Z,0,The golie isn't even trying to save shots,M6mpXtMm93M,the golie isn t even trying to save shots,positive,0.4939,"['golie isn', 'golie', 'save shots']",[],32
@ajanramani5594,2026-06-30T14:48:34Z,0,Messi is the goat🐐🇦🇷🫅,M6mpXtMm93M,messi is the goat,neutral,0.0,"['messi goat', 'messi', 'goat']","[('messi', 'PERSON')]",52
@nishad-u8m,2026-06-30T14:37:28Z,0,Goat 🐐 vs Messi New Battle,M6mpXtMm93M,goat vs messi new battle,negative,-0.3818,"['goat vs', 'vs messi', 'messi new']","[('goat vs messi', 'PERSON')]",58
@RajeshBhuda,2026-06-30T14:34:18Z,0,Messi is the best ❤,M6mpXtMm93M,messi is the best,positive,0.6369,"['messi best', 'messi', 'best']","[('messi', 'PERSON')]",3
@mdmuradhasan5034,2026-06-30T14:33:02Z,0,GOAT LEO 🐐,M6mpXtMm93M,goat leo,neutral,0.0,[],"[('leo', 'ORG')]",21
@RaajkuarSarma,2026-06-30T14:21:48Z,0,This tutorial is clear and easy to follow I enjoyed every second of it.,M6mpXtMm93M,this tutorial is clear and easy to follow i enjoyed every second of it,positive,0.8316,"['tutorial', 'tutorial clear', 'easy follow']",[],111
@leonardonmedeiros,2026-06-30T14:17:29Z,0,BETS shall END NOW!!!! These goals are OUTRAGEOUS,M6mpXtMm93M,bets shall end now these goals are outrageous,negative,-0.4588,"['goals outrageous', 'bets shall', 'bets']",[],17
@AnonyoZarifAkand,2026-06-30T14:02:18Z,0,0:14 Wdym Messi couldn't have done it better?,M6mpXtMm93M,0 14 what do you mean messi couldn t have done it better,positive,0.4404,"['messi couldn', 'messi', 'mean messi']","[('messi couldn', 'PERSON')]",138
@Sentinella911,2026-06-30T13:47:29Z,1,That Jordan goalie let the ball pass him by!  What’s that all about?,M6mpXtMm93M,that jordan goalie let the ball pass him by what s that all about,neutral,0.0,"['jordan goalie', 'ball pass', 'goalie let']","[('jordan', 'GPE')]",57
@ସଫଳତା_ର_ରାସ୍ତା,2026-06-30T13:33:34Z,0,Which team champion FIFA World Cup 2026,M6mpXtMm93M,which team champion fifa world cup 2026,positive,0.5994,"['cup 2026', 'champion fifa', '2026']",[],72
@리비아의게롤트51,2026-06-30T13:30:38Z,1,🇦🇷🇦🇷🇦🇷🇦🇷🇦🇷,M6mpXtMm93M,,neutral,0.0,[],[],0
@ingreedarauz1932,2026-06-30T13:30:36Z,0,Bro rhe goalkeeper let messi score that,M6mpXtMm93M,brother rhe goalkeeper let messi score that,neutral,0.0,"['messi score', 'messi', 'let messi']","[('rhe goalkeeper', 'PERSON'), ('messi', 'PERSON')]",-1
@ElproYt-j3i9e,2026-06-30T13:00:52Z,0,Messi🇦🇷✨ goat,M6mpXtMm93M,messi goat,neutral,0.0,"['messi goat', 'messi', 'goat']","[('messi goat', 'PERSON')]",58
@RonnieFreas,2026-06-30T12:46:49Z,0,Cr7 - the goat!,M6mpXtMm93M,cr7 the goat,neutral,0.0,"['cr7 goat', 'cr7', 'goat']","[('cr7', 'PERSON')]",98
@saranshLakra-f9j,2026-06-30T12:08:34Z,0,The content is well made I will definitely recommend this.,M6mpXtMm93M,the content is well made i will definitely recommend this,positive,0.743,"['content definitely', 'definitely recommend', 'content']",[],94
@AbdulwahabBadrAl-Jabri,2026-06-30T11:59:42Z,0,This channel is amazing It made my day better.,M6mpXtMm93M,this channel is amazing it made my day better,positive,0.7717,"['channel amazing', 'channel', 'day better']",[],69
@MaximStarikov-v6l,2026-06-30T11:07:33Z,0,Why you published it in one month?,M6mpXtMm93M,why you published it in one month,neutral,0.0,"['published month', 'month', 'published']",[],-1
@MaryMcCool-j4f5l,2026-06-30T10:58:03Z,0,This channel is clear and easy to follow This deserves recognition.,M6mpXtMm93M,this channel is clear and easy to follow this deserves recognition,positive,0.6705,"['deserves recognition', 'channel', 'channel clear']",[],69
@DenkAngie,2026-06-30T10:52:53Z,1,The idea is clear and easy to follow I really appreciate the effort.,M6mpXtMm93M,the idea is clear and easy to follow i really appreciate the effort,positive,0.8173,"['idea clear', 'easy follow', 'appreciate effort']",[],51
@AshokSingh-ld2ve,2026-06-30T10:45:04Z,0,The production quality is well made It helped me understand better.,M6mpXtMm93M,the production quality is well made it helped me understand better,positive,0.6124,"['production quality', 'quality helped', 'quality']",[],92
@DaneshVanjara-t1m,2026-06-30T10:08:47Z,0,Amazing video! Thanks for sharing.,M6mpXtMm93M,amazing video thanks for sharing,positive,0.8591,"['amazing video', 'video thanks', 'thanks sharing']",[],118
@AngelaJackson-e9s,2026-06-30T10:08:20Z,0,This channel is outstanding I really appreciate the effort.,M6mpXtMm93M,this channel is outstanding i really appreciate the effort,positive,0.7902,"['channel outstanding', 'really appreciate', 'appreciate effort']",[],69
@LeoneCarlGluntia,2026-06-30T10:05:33Z,0,Veer,M6mpXtMm93M,veer,neutral,0.0,[],[],31
@TousifKhandekar,2026-06-30T09:26:49Z,1,The jordanian goalie seemed like he was playing from the Argentinian side,M6mpXtMm93M,the jordanian goalie seemed like he was playing from the argentinian side,positive,0.5106,"['jordanian goalie', 'playing argentinian', 'argentinian']",[],-1
@Rgaluks,2026-06-30T09:15:19Z,0,Papa Fifa gives Messi penalty and he misses😂😂😂,M6mpXtMm93M,papa fifa gives messi penalty and he misses,negative,-0.5994,"['messi penalty', 'penalty misses', 'gives messi']","[('fifa', 'ORG'), ('messi penalty', 'PERSON')]",65
@AnandGarige087,2026-06-30T08:14:06Z,0,The way you present is top notch I enjoyed every second of it.,M6mpXtMm93M,the way you present is top notch i enjoyed every second of it,positive,0.6249,"['enjoyed second', 'notch enjoyed', 'enjoyed']",[],94
@immortalbroly8150,2026-06-30T08:12:41Z,0,fifa boy 😂😂,M6mpXtMm93M,fifa boy,neutral,0.0,[],"[('fifa', 'ORG')]",10
@AsifSilawat,2026-06-30T08:04:33Z,0,The random person who like my comment I wish your parents live more than 100 years❤,M6mpXtMm93M,the random person who like my comment i wish your parents live more than 100 years,positive,0.6369,"['100 years', 'wish parents', 'parents live']",[],-1
@unnamedkite,2026-06-30T07:56:53Z,1,FIFAs baby boy.,M6mpXtMm93M,fifas baby boy,neutral,0.0,"['fifas baby', 'fifas', 'baby boy']",[],10
@sonupillichappal_official,2026-06-30T07:39:14Z,0,Messi❤,M6mpXtMm93M,messi,neutral,0.0,[],"[('messi', 'PERSON')]",3
@normalsecularist4321,2026-06-30T07:27:58Z,0,Messi goat,M6mpXtMm93M,messi goat,neutral,0.0,"['messi goat', 'messi', 'goat']","[('messi goat', 'PERSON')]",58
@hairulnizam_awe,2026-06-30T07:23:05Z,0,"Just see....  this is world cup, not friendly match...",M6mpXtMm93M,just see this is world cup not friendly match,negative,-0.3875,"['friendly match', 'cup friendly', 'world cup']",[],10
@TaimNalawi,2026-06-30T07:12:27Z,0,No RONALDO IS THE GOAT,M6mpXtMm93M,no ronaldo is the goat,negative,-0.296,"['ronaldo goat', 'ronaldo', 'goat']",[],40
@DanhThếdanh-y2b,2026-06-30T07:05:46Z,3,Messi is the best and he just scored this goal.,M6mpXtMm93M,messi is the best and he just scored this goal,positive,0.6369,"['messi best', 'messi', 'scored goal']","[('messi', 'PERSON')]",3
@grosboxon3445,2026-06-30T06:58:43Z,0,Argentina lucky with the draw as usual,M6mpXtMm93M,argentina lucky with the draw as usual,positive,0.4215,"['argentina lucky', 'lucky draw', 'argentina']","[('argentina', 'GPE')]",53
@shivanshuroy6992,2026-06-30T06:52:43Z,0,VAMOS ARGENTINA 🇦🇷🇦🇷🇦🇷❤️❤️❤️,M6mpXtMm93M,vamos argentina,neutral,0.0,"['vamos argentina', 'vamos', 'argentina']","[('vamos argentina', 'PERSON')]",116
@shivanshuroy6992,2026-06-30T06:52:25Z,0,GOAT MESSI 🇦🇷🇦🇷🇦🇷❤️❤️❤️,M6mpXtMm93M,goat messi,neutral,0.0,"['goat messi', 'messi', 'goat']","[('goat messi', 'PERSON')]",58
@abuukassim-s3g,2026-06-30T06:22:47Z,0,No messi goat goat Are Ronaldo tiam,M6mpXtMm93M,no messi goat goat are ronaldo tiam,negative,-0.296,"['messi goat', 'goat ronaldo', 'messi']",[],52
@Talitonu-t5p,2026-06-30T05:59:29Z,0,cr7 can't score that type of free kick,M6mpXtMm93M,cr7 can t score that type of free kick,positive,0.5106,"['cr7 score', 'free kick', 'cr7']","[('cr7', 'PERSON')]",119
@ireneuszsiedleck9947,2026-06-30T05:52:56Z,0,Tackar.....,M6mpXtMm93M,tackar,neutral,0.0,[],"[('tackar', 'PERSON')]",31
@DustinJustin-y3m,2026-06-30T05:36:23Z,0,The greatest player to ever play the beautiful game ❤,M6mpXtMm93M,the greatest player to ever play the beautiful game,positive,0.8885,"['greatest player', 'play beautiful', 'beautiful game']",[],68
@ahamedrifat2001,2026-06-30T05:23:51Z,1,𝐌𝐞𝐬𝐬𝐢 𝐢𝐬 𝐭𝐡𝐞 𝐫𝐞𝐚𝐥 𝐜𝐨𝐦𝐩𝐥𝐞𝐭𝐞𝐝 𝐆𝐎𝐀𝐓 🐐🇦🇷👑,M6mpXtMm93M,𝐌𝐞𝐬𝐬𝐢 𝐢𝐬 𝐭𝐡𝐞 𝐫𝐞𝐚𝐥 𝐜𝐨𝐦𝐩𝐥𝐞𝐭𝐞𝐝 𝐆𝐎𝐀𝐓,neutral,0.0,"['𝐭𝐡𝐞 𝐫𝐞𝐚𝐥', '𝐫𝐞𝐚𝐥 𝐜𝐨𝐦𝐩𝐥𝐞𝐭𝐞𝐝', '𝐢𝐬 𝐭𝐡𝐞']","[('𝐫𝐞𝐚𝐥', 'GPE'), ('𝐆𝐎𝐀𝐓', 'ORG')]",127
@nurarihayon,2026-06-30T05:03:51Z,0,free lebann. gza u fknn ixrail,M6mpXtMm93M,free lebann gza you fknn ixrail,positive,0.5106,"['free lebann', 'lebann gza', 'lebann']","[('free lebann', 'PERSON')]",-1
@alejandroandrada5182,2026-06-30T04:55:03Z,1,♥♥MESSI ♥♥,M6mpXtMm93M,messi,neutral,0.0,[],"[('messi', 'PERSON')]",3
@lucy123-q1y,2026-06-30T04:51:18Z,0,That penalty was bs all refs have been the worse refereeing ever,M6mpXtMm93M,that penalty was bullshit all refs have been the worse refereeing ever,negative,-0.872,"['bullshit refs', 'penalty bullshit', 'worse refereeing']",[],106
@arnelvillanueva5898,2026-06-30T04:13:21Z,0,Hiram p more😅😅😅😅😅😅😅😅,M6mpXtMm93M,hiram p more,neutral,0.0,['hiram'],[],105
@عزييماني-ي6ظ,2026-06-30T03:45:49Z,1,ياسلام عليكم مبارة ولا اروع,M6mpXtMm93M,ياسلام عليكم مبارة ولا اروع,neutral,0.0,"['ياسلام عليكم', 'عليكم مبارة', 'ياسلام']",[],9
@samueltam6724,2026-06-30T03:33:46Z,1,"The penalty was nonsense. 
The attacker dove down to head the ball, while the defender just naturally cleared it with his foot. I mean, what's wrong with kicking the ball in football? The contact was below the waist—was the defender expected to dive down and head it away too? If anything, the attacker should be called for dangerous play.",M6mpXtMm93M,the penalty was nonsense the attacker dove down to head the ball while the defender just naturally cleared it with his foot i mean what s wrong with kicking the ball in football the contact was below the waist was the defender expected to dive down and head it away too if anything the attacker should be called for dangerous play,negative,-0.9403,"['penalty nonsense', 'penalty', 'kicking ball']",[],-1
@Azmklssxsalo,2026-06-30T03:29:05Z,1,The keeper is argentinas spy,M6mpXtMm93M,the keeper is argentinas spy,neutral,0.0,"['keeper argentinas', 'argentinas spy', 'keeper']",[],32
@BrazilianSammySpyder67,2026-06-30T03:27:53Z,0,MESSI SO TUFF!!!!😝🐐🇦🇷👑,M6mpXtMm93M,messi so tough,negative,-0.2006,"['messi tough', 'messi', 'tough']","[('messi', 'PERSON')]",3
@izmovic,2026-06-30T03:23:33Z,0,Chill it’s just Jordan lol pessi,M6mpXtMm93M,chill it s just jordan laughing out loud pessi,positive,0.4939,"['jordan laughing', 'just jordan', 'jordan']","[('jordan', 'GPE')]",57
@angelykay007,2026-06-30T03:02:57Z,0,Ankara Messi ❤😊,M6mpXtMm93M,ankara messi,neutral,0.0,"['ankara messi', 'ankara', 'messi']","[('ankara messi', 'PERSON')]",20
@deepakhem,2026-06-30T02:16:40Z,1,We all love MESSI ❤❤😊😊😊🎉🎉🎉,M6mpXtMm93M,we all love messi,positive,0.6369,"['love messi', 'messi', 'love']","[('messi', 'PERSON')]",3
@MemonaImran-q5z,2026-06-30T02:12:03Z,1,Chal laura😊,M6mpXtMm93M,chal laura,neutral,0.0,"['chal laura', 'laura', 'chal']","[('chal laura', 'PERSON')]",-1
@LimaAkter-x9k6p,2026-06-30T02:10:12Z,0,🇦🇷🇦🇷🇦🇷🇦🇷🇦🇷🇦🇷❤❤❤,M6mpXtMm93M,,neutral,0.0,[],[],0
@Seangsiden,2026-06-30T01:44:44Z,1,Pepsi the pig,M6mpXtMm93M,pepsi the pig,neutral,0.0,"['pepsi pig', 'pepsi', 'pig']","[('pepsi', 'ORG')]",21
@TamannaAkther-uh7ev,2026-06-30T01:37:15Z,0,🇦🇷🇦🇷🇦🇷😢😢🎉🇦🇷🇦🇷😊,M6mpXtMm93M,,neutral,0.0,[],[],0
@LarsLackman,2026-06-30T01:13:44Z,0,Your explanation is very impressive This deserves recognition.,M6mpXtMm93M,your explanation is very impressive this deserves recognition,positive,0.5563,"['explanation impressive', 'deserves recognition', 'impressive deserves']",[],59
@JBabu-l9g,2026-06-30T01:02:54Z,0,The idea is clear and easy to follow It made my day better.,M6mpXtMm93M,the idea is clear and easy to follow it made my day better,positive,0.8126,"['idea clear', 'follow day', 'easy follow']",[],51
@primatajenius28,2026-06-30T00:49:15Z,0,🎉🎉🎉🎉🎉🎉,M6mpXtMm93M,,neutral,0.0,[],[],0
@dontatmi,2026-06-30T00:22:36Z,0,Messi is literally judgment,M6mpXtMm93M,messi is literally judgment,neutral,0.0,"['messi literally', 'messi', 'literally judgment']","[('messi', 'PERSON')]",3
@MalsawmTonsing,2026-06-30T00:10:16Z,0,😂😂😂😂😂e😂😂😂😂😂😂😂😂,M6mpXtMm93M,e,neutral,0.0,[],[],64
@WaldFUGrngoo,2026-06-30T00:01:25Z,0,So what actual tier teams did argentina play against?,M6mpXtMm93M,so what actual tier teams did argentina play against,positive,0.34,"['argentina play', 'tier teams', 'did argentina']","[('argentina', 'GPE')]",53
@GabrielleWallace-v8x2f,2026-06-29T23:44:54Z,0,Messy is the Goat🇦🇷🇦🇷🇦🇷🇦🇷 my dad loves you Messy 🇦🇷🇦🇷🇦🇷🇦🇷🇦🇷🇦🇷👑,M6mpXtMm93M,messy is the goat my dad loves you messy,negative,-0.0772,"['messy goat', 'loves messy', 'messy']",[],21
@ArielOquendo10,2026-06-29T23:41:58Z,0,REGALADO NI DISUMULAN AHORA.,M6mpXtMm93M,regalado no idea disumulan ahora,negative,-0.296,"['regalado', 'disumulan ahora', 'regalado idea']","[('disumulan ahora', 'PERSON')]",4
@Dutchsparrow1908,2026-06-29T23:37:43Z,1,WORD ON THE STREET IS THE GOALKEEPER IS THE BIGGEST MESSI FAN!! Lol 😂😂😂,M6mpXtMm93M,word on the street is the goalkeeper is the biggest messi fan laughing out loud,positive,0.6705,"['messi fan', 'messi', 'biggest messi']",[],3
@SitoTiger,2026-06-29T23:35:24Z,0,Mexico 🇲🇽,M6mpXtMm93M,mexico,neutral,0.0,[],"[('mexico', 'GPE')]",53
@raghum8905,2026-06-29T23:33:03Z,1,Jordan goal keeper 😂😂😂not try..stop 🛑😂😂😂,M6mpXtMm93M,jordan goal keeper not try stop,positive,0.2235,"['keeper try', 'goal keeper', 'jordan goal']","[('jordan', 'GPE')]",57
@jhonatanmoreno866,2026-06-29T23:19:04Z,1,Ese arquero no atrapa nada,M6mpXtMm93M,ese arquero no atrapa nada,negative,-0.296,"['atrapa nada', 'ese arquero', 'arquero atrapa']","[('nada', 'ORG')]",4
@harrisontafea7680,2026-06-29T23:11:08Z,0,Goat doing goat things 💯,M6mpXtMm93M,goat doing goat things,neutral,0.0,"['goat doing', 'doing goat', 'goat']",[],21
@HakanDemirtaş34,2026-06-29T22:57:46Z,0,"Amerika'nın yolunu açmak için her anormalliği izliyoruz. Paraguay Almanya maçı hakemi , Almanya'nın penaltısında VAR a gitmedi, golünü iptal etti. Arkadan yapılan faullere sarı kart vermedi... Paraguay futbolun çirkin yüzü.",M6mpXtMm93M,amerika nın yolunu açmak için her anormalliği izliyoruz paraguay almanya maçı hakemi almanya nın penaltısında var a gitmedi golünü iptal etti arkadan yapılan faullere sarı kart vermedi paraguay futbolun çirkin yüzü,neutral,0.0,"['paraguay futbolun', 'vermedi paraguay', 'paraguay']","[('anormalliği izliyoruz', 'PERSON'), ('paraguay', 'ORG'), ('almanya maçı hakemi almanya', 'PERSON'), ('arkadan yapılan faullere', 'ORG'), ('paraguay', 'ORG'), ('futbolun çirkin', 'PERSON')]",-1
@Drizzy676,2026-06-29T22:38:27Z,0,Messi comes messi scores,M6mpXtMm93M,messi comes messi scores,neutral,0.0,"['messi scores', 'messi comes', 'comes messi']","[('messi', 'PERSON'), ('messi', 'PERSON')]",-1
@SergejBohl-m6v,2026-06-29T22:04:58Z,0,FC Messi. ⚽️⚽️⚽️⚽️⚽️⚽️⚽️⚽️⚽️⚽️⚽️⚽️⚽️⚽️⚽️⚽️⚽️⚽️⚽️⚽️,M6mpXtMm93M,fruit cake messi,neutral,0.0,"['cake messi', 'fruit cake', 'messi']","[('messi', 'PERSON')]",3
@Ant1Z10n,2026-06-29T21:53:27Z,0,"0:14 ""Messi couldn't have done it better""
1:37 Messi did it better",M6mpXtMm93M,0 14 messi couldn t have done it better 1 37 messi did it better,positive,0.7003,"['14 messi', '37 messi', 'messi couldn']",[],138
@diamondomar111,2026-06-29T21:38:52Z,0,STOP SHOWING THE SCORES‼️‼️‼️😡😡😤😤,M6mpXtMm93M,stop showing the scores,negative,-0.296,"['showing scores', 'scores', 'stop showing']",[],99
@DavidClark-z3y,2026-06-29T21:31:25Z,0,2022 cup was cheerleading for Argentina so let’s hope this one isn’t.  Biased referees and sheeple fans are by far the most unappealing thing about this sport which I love btw.,M6mpXtMm93M,2022 cup was cheerleading for argentina so let s hope this one isn t biased referees and sheeple fans are by far the most unappealing thing about this sport which i love by the way,positive,0.8158,"['cheerleading argentina', 'referees sheeple', 'cup cheerleading']","[('argentina', 'GPE')]",-1
@DavidClark-z3y,2026-06-29T21:27:51Z,0,"In a fair match which does often happens, the score should be 1-1 since one is a rigged penalty and the other involved the Jordanian goalie having a soft spot for the overrated Messi.",M6mpXtMm93M,in a fair match which does often happens the score should be 1 1 since one is a rigged penalty and the other involved the jordanian goalie having a soft spot for the overrated messi,negative,-0.4939,"['rigged penalty', 'happens score', 'score rigged']",[],138
@DavidClark-z3y,2026-06-29T21:25:24Z,1,"Poor Jordan, they were playing against Argentina and the referee",M6mpXtMm93M,poor jordan they were playing against argentina and the referee,negative,-0.3182,"['argentina referee', 'poor jordan', 'playing argentina']","[('jordan', 'GPE'), ('argentina', 'GPE')]",-1
@etienneandrs,2026-06-29T21:11:27Z,0,"El portero se para detrás de la barrera en lugar de al lado donde no hay barrera , increíble o scripted ?",M6mpXtMm93M,el portero se para detrás de la barrera en lugar de al lado donde no hay barrera increíble Oh scripted,negative,-0.296,"['la barrera', 'barrera en', 'portero se']","[('el portero', 'PERSON'), ('para detrás de la', 'PERSON'), ('en lugar de al lado', 'PERSON')]",4
@sunusiyusuf-u3y,2026-06-29T20:54:31Z,0,Your explanation is exactly what I needed It deserves more views.,M6mpXtMm93M,your explanation is exactly what i needed it deserves more views,neutral,0.0,"['deserves views', 'explanation exactly', 'explanation']",[],59
@dalejokhan8264,2026-06-29T20:52:33Z,0,Fifa should add an award for accuracy. Most accurate player. Testing the keeper is important.,M6mpXtMm93M,fifa should add an award for accuracy most accurate player testing the keeper is important,positive,0.6486,"['keeper important', 'award accuracy', 'testing keeper']","[('fifa', 'ORG')]",32
@henryvasquez3312,2026-06-29T20:32:16Z,2,"I’m glad Messi is enjoying football, he’s basically 99 in almost every aspect and is just doing side quest scoring goal after goal",M6mpXtMm93M,i am glad messi is enjoying football he s basically 99 in almost every aspect and is just doing side quest scoring goal after goal,positive,0.7506,"['messi enjoying', 'glad messi', 'messi']","[('glad messi', 'PERSON')]",3
@MatiasbordonCN,2026-06-29T20:19:26Z,0,🇦🇷🇦🇷🇦🇷,M6mpXtMm93M,,neutral,0.0,[],[],0
@EmmanuelNwachukwuma,2026-06-29T20:10:37Z,0,One thing for sure is?! Never use a free kick to bully Messi,M6mpXtMm93M,one thing for sure is never use a free kick to bully messi,negative,-0.5577,"['bully messi', 'free kick', 'messi']","[('messi', 'PERSON')]",65
@Baran9182,2026-06-29T20:03:09Z,0,"Oh messsi couldn’t have done it better 
When Messi took the free kick 
…",M6mpXtMm93M,oh messsi couldn t have done it better when messi took the free kick,positive,0.7351,"['messi took', 'better messi', 'messi']","[('messi', 'PERSON')]",65
@Oásdofigáss,2026-06-29T20:02:03Z,0,Vini e Júnior Deus te abençoe nessa copa e outras você merce nessa copa campeão joga o endrick sagrado seja o coração de Deus amém primeiro ouro depois prata para nós Brasil 🇧🇷,M6mpXtMm93M,vini e júnior deus Team effort abençoe nessa copa e outras você merce nessa copa campeão joga Oh endrick sagrado seja Oh coração de deus amém primeiro ouro depois prata para nós brasil,neutral,0.0,"['coração deus', 'copa campeão', 'nós brasil']","[('nessa', 'ORG'), ('primeiro ouro', 'PERSON'), ('para nós brasil', 'PERSON')]",4
@AnaMariaMagassoMagasso,2026-06-29T19:59:09Z,0,Messiiiiiiiiii vamos,M6mpXtMm93M,messiiiiiiiiii vamos,neutral,0.0,"['messiiiiiiiiii vamos', 'messiiiiiiiiii', 'vamos']","[('messiiiiiiiiii vamos', 'PERSON')]",116
@manishbhardwaj3242,2026-06-29T19:58:24Z,5,0:41 Raj Shamani scores penalty for Argentina.,M6mpXtMm93M,0 41 raj shamani scores penalty for argentina,negative,-0.4588,"['shamani scores', 'penalty argentina', 'raj shamani']","[('argentina', 'GPE')]",-1
@HenryAuca,2026-06-29T19:57:43Z,0,😊,M6mpXtMm93M,,neutral,0.0,[],[],0
@juanignaciofranceschini8915,2026-06-29T19:25:55Z,0,"Messi is sooo happy, I'm just rooting for Argentina to see his face full of happiness, he is the GOAT!",M6mpXtMm93M,messi is sooo happy i am just rooting for argentina to see his face full of happiness he is the goat,positive,0.8074,"['messi sooo', 'messi', 'rooting argentina']","[('messi', 'PERSON'), ('argentina', 'GPE')]",52
@SergioSuarez-s4l,2026-06-29T19:18:58Z,0,🇦🇷😂🐐🫅,M6mpXtMm93M,,neutral,0.0,[],[],0
@utubetalks2359,2026-06-29T19:14:46Z,2,The jordan keeper hesitate to move his body,M6mpXtMm93M,the jordan keeper hesitate to move his body,negative,-0.2732,"['jordan keeper', 'keeper hesitate', 'jordan']","[('jordan', 'GPE')]",57
@srijalrijal4261,2026-06-29T19:02:54Z,0,"¡Vamos, Argentina!🇦🇷⚽🩵🤍😍🥰🥹🫶🔥🔥🔥🔥",M6mpXtMm93M,vamos argentina,neutral,0.0,"['vamos argentina', 'vamos', 'argentina']","[('vamos argentina', 'PERSON')]",116
@SaberRf-o4r,2026-06-29T18:48:20Z,0,This performance is outstanding It helped me understand better.,M6mpXtMm93M,this performance is outstanding it helped me understand better,positive,0.7845,"['performance outstanding', 'performance', 'outstanding helped']",[],55
@akashnath6959,2026-06-29T18:41:13Z,1,"YouTube comment section is very different from Instagram , this proves that Messi Haters and Ronaldo Fans are all reel watchers they don't even watch live matches neither highlights . They see fascinating reels of Ronaldo playing football 10-15 years back and become fan and troll Messi.",M6mpXtMm93M,youtube comment section is very different from instagram this proves that messi haters and ronaldo fans are all reel watchers they denial of normal t even watch live matches neither highlights they see fascinating reels of ronaldo playing football 10 15 years back and become fan and person who diliberately stirs up trouble messi,positive,0.1779,"['messi haters', 'haters ronaldo', 'ronaldo fans']","[('messi', 'PERSON'), ('ronaldo', 'ORG')]",108
@screwbigtechsanti-sciencem9438,2026-06-29T18:34:20Z,0,"Remove ALL of Messi's goals and he is still the GOAT and the combination of Maradona and Cruyff. He is still man of the match candidate in almost ever single game he ever played. THAT is what makes him the GOAT. This is not the sport of goalball or shootball (looking at you, the childish, shallow, dumb CR7 fans), this is the beautiful game. This is football. This is Messi.
The GOAT by a million miles. Absolutely no one comes close except the combination of Pele, Maradona and Cruyff. If those three players fused into one, they would be CLOSE to Messi's level, but still not quite there. THAT is why he is the GOAT bar none, zero debate, if you think you have an argument, you have minus IQ.",M6mpXtMm93M,remove all of messi s goals and he is still the goat and the combination of maradona and cruyff he is still man of the match candidate in almost ever single game he ever played that is what makes him the goat this is not the sport of goalball or shootball looking at you the childish shallow dumb cr7 fans this is the beautiful game this is football this is messi the goat by a million miles absolutely no one comes close except the combination of pele maradona and cruyff if those three players fused into one they would be close to messi s level but still not quite there that is why he is the goat bar none zero debate if you think you have an argument you have minus iq,negative,-0.5569,"['messi goat', 'messi', 'remove messi']","[('messi s', 'PERSON'), ('pele maradona', 'PERSON'), ('messi', 'PERSON')]",52
@Goknes66,2026-06-29T18:30:26Z,1,"1:40 ذكرني بحارس لعبة فيفا و بيس
يطالع على الكورة و هي تدخل😂😂😂😂",M6mpXtMm93M,1 40 ذكرني بحارس لعبة فيفا و بيس يطالع على الكورة و هي تدخل,neutral,0.0,"['40 ذكرني', 'ذكرني بحارس', 'ذكرني']","[('على الكورة', 'ORG')]",9
@lianli_lngshot,2026-06-29T18:23:19Z,19,1:46 He didn’t even try to catch the ball..,M6mpXtMm93M,1 46 he didn t even try to catch the ball,neutral,0.0,"['46 didn', 'catch ball', '46']",[],-1
@Glittery.h,2026-06-29T18:22:53Z,0,Respect for the beautiful goal that jordan scored !,M6mpXtMm93M,respect for the beautiful goal that jordan scored,positive,0.7906,"['goal jordan', 'jordan scored', 'beautiful goal']","[('jordan', 'GPE')]",57
@Liza-888k,2026-06-29T18:09:51Z,2,Why does everyone play so fake,M6mpXtMm93M,why does everyone play so fake,negative,-0.38,"['play fake', 'fake', 'play']",[],-1
@infinityDrifterLK,2026-06-29T17:57:04Z,0,Speed Hi,M6mpXtMm93M,speed hi,neutral,0.0,[],[],-1
@timilsinasanta5087,2026-06-29T17:50:44Z,0,Lado kha,M6mpXtMm93M,lado kha,neutral,0.0,[],"[('lado kha', 'PERSON')]",11
@suraj-travel_n_garden-tales,2026-06-29T17:23:06Z,0,What was the meaning of that flag,M6mpXtMm93M,what was the meaning of that flag,neutral,0.0,"['meaning flag', 'flag', 'meaning']",[],90
@AnishRoy77-c1q,2026-06-29T17:18:03Z,0,Your father is brazil 🇧🇷 from India 🇮🇳,M6mpXtMm93M,your father is brazil from india,neutral,0.0,"['father brazil', 'brazil india', 'father']","[('brazil', 'GPE'), ('india', 'GPE')]",73
@itsrobiul,2026-06-29T17:10:33Z,1,1:48 easy save but the goalkeeper is messi fan😂,M6mpXtMm93M,1 48 easy save but the goalkeeper is messi fan,positive,0.7184,"['goalkeeper messi', 'save goalkeeper', 'messi']","[('messi', 'PERSON')]",-1
@NexGoated,2026-06-29T17:09:33Z,1,Bribed gk 😂😂,M6mpXtMm93M,bribed gk,neutral,0.0,[],[],-1
@rathishatutube,2026-06-29T17:02:01Z,0,Worst goalkeeping from jordan😮,M6mpXtMm93M,worst goalkeeping from jordan,negative,-0.6249,"['goalkeeping jordan', 'worst goalkeeping', 'goalkeeping']","[('jordan', 'GPE')]",57
@pradeepvig9880,2026-06-29T17:00:51Z,1,Jordan goalkeeper letting messi score looks fishy,M6mpXtMm93M,jordan goalkeeper letting messi score looks fishy,neutral,0.0,"['messi score', 'messi', 'jordan goalkeeper']","[('jordan', 'GPE')]",65
@AmmarTashildar-e3y,2026-06-29T16:57:18Z,0,No,M6mpXtMm93M,no,negative,-0.296,[],[],70
@AmmarTashildar-e3y,2026-06-29T16:57:12Z,0,No,M6mpXtMm93M,no,negative,-0.296,[],[],70
@AriaTheGoat,2026-06-29T16:53:17Z,2,The goat🐐🇦🇷,M6mpXtMm93M,the goat,neutral,0.0,[],[],21
@zidaneazizi97,2026-06-29T16:47:57Z,0,goalkeeper?,M6mpXtMm93M,goalkeeper,neutral,0.0,['goalkeeper'],[],32
@JeetGhosh2,2026-06-29T16:46:04Z,0,"Who is 🐐 goat
Ronaldo 
Messi 
Mbbape
Sunil india 🇮🇳",M6mpXtMm93M,who is goat ronaldo messi mbbape sunil india,neutral,0.0,"['messi mbbape', 'goat ronaldo', 'messi']","[('messi mbbape', 'PERSON'), ('india', 'GPE')]",58
@ansaridehiya9164,2026-06-29T16:34:43Z,1,"What a kit argentina has❤❤
Very very beautiful 😍",M6mpXtMm93M,what a keep in touch argentina has very very beautiful,positive,0.6674,"['argentina beautiful', 'touch argentina', 'argentina']","[('argentina', 'GPE')]",53
@vinothraj7042,2026-06-29T16:34:15Z,1,How the goal keeper missed to save the easy freekick,M6mpXtMm93M,how the goal keeper missed to save the easy freekick,positive,0.5994,"['keeper missed', 'goal keeper', 'easy freekick']",[],65
@Rwarfootage,2026-06-29T16:34:06Z,0,How much did they pay the goal keeper?,M6mpXtMm93M,how much did they pay the goal keeper,negative,-0.1027,"['goal keeper', 'pay goal', 'keeper']",[],32
@Atombender,2026-06-29T16:27:25Z,0,"For the record, Messi requested being benched first but joined the game shortly after Jordan scored. And then of course scored as well 20 min later.",M6mpXtMm93M,for the record messi requested being benched first but joined the game shortly after jordan scored and then of course scored as well 20 minute later,positive,0.3919,"['jordan scored', 'messi requested', 'messi']","[('jordan', 'GPE')]",138
@ElsonJona123,2026-06-29T16:20:40Z,0,"messi,messi,messimesssiiiiiiii gggggggggggggggggggggggggggggoooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaallllllllllllllllllllllllllllllllllllllllll",M6mpXtMm93M,messi messi messimesssiiiiiiii gggggggggggggggggggggggggggggoooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaallllllllllllllllllllllllllllllllllllllllll,neutral,0.0,"['messi messimesssiiiiiiii', 'messimesssiiiiiiii gggggggggggggggggggggggggggggoooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaallllllllllllllllllllllllllllllllllllllllll', 'messimesssiiiiiiii']","[('messi messi', 'PERSON'), ('gggggggggggggggggggggggggggggoooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaallllllllllllllllllllllllllllllllllllllllll', 'GPE')]",3
@morrismessi,2026-06-29T16:11:17Z,0,He is the greatest thsi guy is crazy,M6mpXtMm93M,he is the greatest thsi guy is crazy,positive,0.4215,"['guy crazy', 'greatest thsi', 'thsi guy']",[],36
@RohitTamang-r7e,2026-06-29T16:03:35Z,0,We miss dimaria ❤,M6mpXtMm93M,we miss dimaria,negative,-0.1531,"['miss dimaria', 'dimaria', 'miss']",[],-1
@megaramaAtlas-s8c,2026-06-29T15:57:45Z,0,Messi Play only 15 Minutes and Score 🐐,M6mpXtMm93M,messi play only 15 minutes and score,positive,0.34,"['messi play', 'messi', 'minutes score']","[('messi', 'PERSON')]",138
@BishnupriyagoudaBishnupriyagou,2026-06-29T15:54:12Z,0,Messi magic',M6mpXtMm93M,messi magic,neutral,0.0,"['messi magic', 'messi', 'magic']","[('messi magic', 'PERSON')]",3
@BishnupriyagoudaBishnupriyagou,2026-06-29T15:54:04Z,0,Goat Lionel messi forever one and only,M6mpXtMm93M,goat lionel messi forever one and only,neutral,0.0,"['lionel messi', 'messi forever', 'goat lionel']","[('messi', 'PERSON')]",58
@Dmitriy_Miele,2026-06-29T15:52:36Z,0,А сколько получает каждый вратарь и защитник за то что пропускает голы от Месси и даже не пытается брать мяч ?😂😂😂,M6mpXtMm93M,а сколько получает каждый вратарь и защитник за то что пропускает голы от месси и даже не пытается брать мяч,neutral,0.0,"['получает каждый', 'вратарь защитник', 'защитник за']","[('мяч', 'ORG')]",2
@NazirahmadBhat-sz2fm,2026-06-29T15:43:43Z,0,Messi goat,M6mpXtMm93M,messi goat,neutral,0.0,"['messi goat', 'messi', 'goat']","[('messi goat', 'PERSON')]",58
@chipngo9758,2026-06-29T15:43:38Z,2,Messi is getting better by age. If he's not younger I don't know what that is.😅,M6mpXtMm93M,messi is getting better by age if he s not younger i denial of normal t know what that is,positive,0.4404,"['messi', 'messi getting', 'younger']","[('messi', 'PERSON')]",15
@lightseeker1813,2026-06-29T15:42:10Z,134,Jordan's goalkeeper vs Jordan,M6mpXtMm93M,jordan s goalkeeper vs jordan,neutral,0.0,"['jordan goalkeeper', 'vs jordan', 'jordan']","[('jordan s goalkeeper vs', 'PERSON'), ('jordan', 'GPE')]",57
@Rjsagarsonwani,2026-06-29T15:38:19Z,0,Messi =🐐,M6mpXtMm93M,messi,neutral,0.0,[],"[('messi', 'PERSON')]",3
@Dom123kom,2026-06-29T15:33:31Z,0,That Messi free kick wasn't unstoppable,M6mpXtMm93M,that messi free kick wasn t unstoppable,positive,0.3612,"['kick wasn', 'wasn unstoppable', 'messi free']","[('messi free kick', 'PERSON')]",65
@emilsullivan1241,2026-06-29T15:30:03Z,0,The content is top notch I really appreciate the effort.,M6mpXtMm93M,the content is top notch i really appreciate the effort,positive,0.5849,"['really appreciate', 'appreciate effort', 'content notch']",[],94
@ghait7_,2026-06-29T15:29:38Z,0,حارس فاشل لو عامر شفيع كان انتهت تعادل ، هدفين على الحارس,M6mpXtMm93M,حارس فاشل لو عامر شفيع كان انتهت تعادل هدفين على الحارس,neutral,0.0,"['حارس فاشل', 'عامر شفيع', 'شفيع كان']","[('حارس فاشل لو عامر شفيع', 'ORG'), ('على', 'ORG')]",9
@SawsanManal,2026-06-29T15:29:00Z,0,Messi Fans Like,M6mpXtMm93M,messi fans like,positive,0.3612,"['messi fans', 'fans like', 'messi']","[('messi', 'PERSON')]",3
@SunilSunil-v4t2h,2026-06-29T15:23:47Z,0,The way you present is very impressive It deserves more views.,M6mpXtMm93M,the way you present is very impressive it deserves more views,positive,0.5563,"['present impressive', 'deserves views', 'impressive deserves']",[],94
@ShatveerSharat,2026-06-29T15:23:36Z,0,Wow,M6mpXtMm93M,wow,positive,0.5859,[],[],96
@riyadulislam1075,2026-06-29T15:23:24Z,0,❤❤,M6mpXtMm93M,,neutral,0.0,[],[],0
@dddddd9641,2026-06-29T15:21:07Z,0,Месси только вышел и сразу забил,M6mpXtMm93M,месси только вышел и сразу забил,neutral,0.0,"['сразу забил', 'месси только', 'вышел сразу']","[('месси только', 'ORG')]",2
@Alibaba-hd6po,2026-06-29T15:19:11Z,0,"Jordan goalkeeper why standing, better he can sit, can avoid leg pain",M6mpXtMm93M,jordan goalkeeper why standing better he can sit can avoid leg pain,negative,-0.3818,"['leg pain', 'avoid leg', 'jordan goalkeeper']","[('jordan', 'GPE')]",57
@EveryoneIsAmelak,2026-06-29T15:19:06Z,0,Cant wait to see this team lose 😂,M6mpXtMm93M,cant wait to see this team lose,negative,-0.4019,"['team lose', 'lose', 'wait team']",[],-1
@MXO19MC,2026-06-29T15:18:24Z,1,Messi goat,M6mpXtMm93M,messi goat,neutral,0.0,"['messi goat', 'messi', 'goat']","[('messi goat', 'PERSON')]",58
@AfrozaNissat-b5q,2026-06-29T15:17:23Z,0,hey bro messi is not goat,M6mpXtMm93M,hey brother messi is not goat,neutral,0.0,"['messi goat', 'brother messi', 'messi']","[('messi', 'PERSON')]",52
@leontinemccain5170,2026-06-29T15:16:55Z,0,For me they are favorites together with Germany at the moment although you can't discount France. The Netherlands and Belgium might cause an upset.,M6mpXtMm93M,for me they are favorites together with germany at the moment although you can t discount france the netherlands and belgium might cause an upset,positive,0.0516,"['favorites germany', 'netherlands belgium', 'france netherlands']","[('germany', 'GPE'), ('france', 'GPE'), ('netherlands', 'GPE'), ('belgium', 'GPE')]",75
@_KI7A,2026-06-29T15:13:49Z,2,The GOAT right here! 🐐🇦🇷🔥,M6mpXtMm93M,the goat right here,neutral,0.0,"['goat right', 'goat', 'right']",[],21
@ChorshanbiyevOrol,2026-06-29T15:11:40Z,2,Messi king 🤴  world football,M6mpXtMm93M,messi king world football,neutral,0.0,"['messi king', 'messi', 'world football']","[('messi', 'PERSON')]",3
@ChorshanbiyevOrol,2026-06-29T15:11:28Z,1,Congratulations Messi Congratulations Argentina 🇦🇷  from Uzbekistan 🇺🇿,M6mpXtMm93M,congratulations messi congratulations argentina from uzbekistan,positive,0.8316,"['congratulations argentina', 'congratulations messi', 'messi congratulations']","[('messi congratulations', 'PERSON'), ('argentina', 'GPE')]",-1
@AdityaGaware-p7w,2026-06-29T15:10:53Z,3,0:47 worldcup finals??,M6mpXtMm93M,0 47 worldcup finals,neutral,0.0,"['47 worldcup', 'worldcup finals', 'worldcup']",[],17
@IRSPORTTABLETENNIS-p2q,2026-06-29T15:08:37Z,0,GOAT 🐐,M6mpXtMm93M,goat,neutral,0.0,[],[],21
@pj-guwg43Y,2026-06-29T15:01:16Z,3,Messi is alone enough,M6mpXtMm93M,messi is alone enough,negative,-0.25,['messi'],"[('messi', 'PERSON')]",3
@KunalRajput-g9f6f,2026-06-29T15:00:31Z,0,GOAT ❤❤,M6mpXtMm93M,goat,neutral,0.0,[],[],21
@SachinPokharel-y1k,2026-06-29T14:54:58Z,1,Thank you for 6 subscribers 🥺😔🎉,M6mpXtMm93M,thank you for 6 subscribers,positive,0.3612,"['thank subscribers', 'subscribers', 'thank']",[],-1
@SachinPokharel-y1k,2026-06-29T14:54:53Z,1,Thank you for 6 subscribers 🥺😔🎉,M6mpXtMm93M,thank you for 6 subscribers,positive,0.3612,"['thank subscribers', 'subscribers', 'thank']",[],-1
@SachinPokharel-y1k,2026-06-29T14:49:30Z,2,1:24 Thank you for 6 subscribers 🥺😔🎉,M6mpXtMm93M,1 24 thank you for 6 subscribers,positive,0.3612,"['24 thank', '24', 'thank subscribers']",[],-1
@TheSytheOfficial,2026-06-29T14:49:06Z,2,Great victory! And next time Jordan!,M6mpXtMm93M,great victory and next time jordan,positive,0.6249,"['time jordan', 'jordan', 'great victory']","[('jordan', 'GPE')]",57
@deshonthetube,2026-06-29T14:47:56Z,2,"Jordan goal keeper ❎
Jordan goal watcher ✅",M6mpXtMm93M,jordan goal keeper jordan goal watcher,neutral,0.0,"['goal watcher', 'keeper jordan', 'goal keeper']","[('jordan', 'GPE'), ('jordan', 'GPE')]",57
@SachinPokharel-y1k,2026-06-29T14:47:06Z,1,Thank you for 6 subscribers 🥺🥺🎉,M6mpXtMm93M,thank you for 6 subscribers,positive,0.3612,"['thank subscribers', 'subscribers', 'thank']",[],-1
@SachinPokharel-y1k,2026-06-29T14:46:37Z,0,Thank you for 6 subscribers 🥺🎉🎉,M6mpXtMm93M,thank you for 6 subscribers,positive,0.3612,"['thank subscribers', 'subscribers', 'thank']",[],-1
@anawanmoi919,2026-06-29T14:42:15Z,1,Ronaldo is better than Messi.,M6mpXtMm93M,ronaldo is better than messi,positive,0.4404,"['ronaldo better', 'better messi', 'messi']","[('ronaldo', 'ORG'), ('messi', 'PERSON')]",37
@theblackswordzman,2026-06-29T14:41:18Z,0,Scaloni wasted no time in summoning Messiraga after conceding one goal 😂😂,M6mpXtMm93M,scaloni wasted no time in summoning messiraga after conceding one goal,negative,-0.6597,"['scaloni wasted', 'messiraga conceding', 'summoning messiraga']",[],-1
@IqbalArdiansyah-yx6xm,2026-06-29T14:37:40Z,0,pans demit panas dingin wkwkwkwkwkw,M6mpXtMm93M,pans demit panas dingin wkwkwkwkwkw,neutral,0.0,"['pans demit', 'demit panas', 'panas dingin']",[],-1
@pardeepkamal6941,2026-06-29T14:35:27Z,0,😂हा हा,M6mpXtMm93M,ह ह,neutral,0.0,[],[],9
@2519Anan,2026-06-29T14:34:55Z,0,"Congratulations to team Argentina & fans for winning this match!

From a football fan in Thailand.",M6mpXtMm93M,congratulations to team argentina fans for winning this match from a football fan in thailand,positive,0.8625,"['argentina fans', 'team argentina', 'fan thailand']","[('argentina', 'GPE'), ('thailand', 'GPE')]",-1
@ExploringTamizhan,2026-06-29T14:31:52Z,0,Argentina 🇦🇷🐐❗ Messi ✓✓✓✓,M6mpXtMm93M,argentina messi,neutral,0.0,"['argentina messi', 'messi', 'argentina']","[('argentina messi', 'PERSON')]",3
@peacemaker178,2026-06-29T14:31:48Z,0,Messi ❤❤❤,M6mpXtMm93M,messi,neutral,0.0,[],"[('messi', 'PERSON')]",3
@kingkong423324,2026-06-29T14:30:50Z,1,约旦門將絕對係美斯fans,M6mpXtMm93M,约旦門將絕對係美斯fans,neutral,0.0,['约旦門將絕對係美斯fans'],[],1
@IrappaNayak-f3i,2026-06-29T14:30:40Z,0,"Your videos are always so helpful, thank you!",M6mpXtMm93M,your videos are always so helpful thank you,positive,0.7502,"['videos helpful', 'videos', 'helpful thank']",[],-1
@waly3302,2026-06-29T14:18:30Z,0,English commentator are so boring...,M6mpXtMm93M,english commentator are so boring,negative,-0.4572,"['commentator boring', 'english commentator', 'commentator']",[],29
@Alpha_Alpha06,2026-06-29T14:18:25Z,0,Argentina 🇦🇷🐐⭐️⭐️⭐️⭐️,M6mpXtMm93M,argentina,neutral,0.0,[],"[('argentina', 'GPE')]",53
@SinchanGaming16,2026-06-29T14:17:58Z,0,messi 🫶🏻,M6mpXtMm93M,messi,neutral,0.0,[],"[('messi', 'PERSON')]",3
@oroufeyssalchabibogo4305,2026-06-29T14:17:30Z,0,❤❤,M6mpXtMm93M,,neutral,0.0,[],[],0
@나무-m8t,2026-06-29T14:17:24Z,0,"Great job, this video was very useful!",M6mpXtMm93M,great job this video was very useful,positive,0.807,"['great job', 'video useful', 'job video']",[],-1
@marcus3502,2026-06-29T14:11:52Z,0,Messi makes reality look broken,M6mpXtMm93M,messi makes reality look broken,negative,-0.4767,"['messi makes', 'messi', 'look broken']","[('messi', 'PERSON')]",3
@foyazsarkarniber,2026-06-29T14:02:27Z,0,From Bangladesh 🇧🇩❤️‍🩹🇦🇷,M6mpXtMm93M,from bangladesh,neutral,0.0,['bangladesh'],[],87
@새우-h7m,2026-06-29T14:00:40Z,0,The content is amazing I will come back to watch it again.,M6mpXtMm93M,the content is amazing i will come back to watch it again,positive,0.5859,"['content amazing', 'content', 'watch']",[],-1
@MiladFahim-f7r,2026-06-29T13:57:14Z,1,Congratulations !,M6mpXtMm93M,congratulations,positive,0.5994,['congratulations'],[],-1
@kazzi611,2026-06-29T13:54:23Z,0,Jordan out,M6mpXtMm93M,jordan out,neutral,0.0,['jordan'],"[('jordan', 'GPE')]",57
@kickonsunday,2026-06-29T13:45:43Z,0,my goat messi letsgooow,M6mpXtMm93M,my goat messi letsgooow,neutral,0.0,"['goat messi', 'messi letsgooow', 'messi']",[],58
@macheranojr,2026-06-29T13:41:27Z,1,El verdadero GOAT es CR7 🐐🇵🇹,M6mpXtMm93M,el verdadero goat es cr7,neutral,0.0,"['es cr7', 'goat es', 'verdadero goat']","[('cr7', 'PERSON')]",-1
@Crowd-Roar,2026-06-29T13:34:13Z,0,Who king of football ⚽😊,M6mpXtMm93M,who king of football,neutral,0.0,"['king football', 'king', 'football']",[],-1
@RubinaEnglengpi,2026-06-29T13:33:24Z,0,Meesi is battery then Ronaldo ❤❤❤,M6mpXtMm93M,meesi is battery then ronaldo,neutral,0.0,"['battery ronaldo', 'meesi battery', 'ronaldo']",[],13
@Dg-rd2uj,2026-06-29T13:29:47Z,0,Didn't move because they are out of the fwc,M6mpXtMm93M,didn t move because they are out of the fwc,neutral,0.0,"['didn fwc', 'fwc', 'didn']",[],-1
@seemadessai4212,2026-06-29T13:28:08Z,0,Messi the goat,M6mpXtMm93M,messi the goat,neutral,0.0,"['messi goat', 'messi', 'goat']","[('messi', 'PERSON')]",58
@ZaforAhamad-s5h,2026-06-29T13:27:18Z,0,👌👌👌👌😘🇧🇩🇧🇩🇧🇩🇧🇩🇧🇩❤️‍🩹❤️‍🩹❤️‍🩹,M6mpXtMm93M,,neutral,0.0,[],[],0
@DebraMiller-w1d,2026-06-29T13:23:14Z,0,This tutorial is clear and easy to follow I will definitely recommend this.,M6mpXtMm93M,this tutorial is clear and easy to follow i will definitely recommend this,positive,0.8658,"['tutorial', 'tutorial clear', 'definitely recommend']",[],111
@sahilkalsulkar3192,2026-06-29T13:20:15Z,2,Why the goalkeeper didn't even tried?,M6mpXtMm93M,why the goalkeeper didn t even tried,neutral,0.0,"['goalkeeper didn', 'goalkeeper', 'didn tried']",[],32
@latenty,2026-06-29T13:11:35Z,0,Thumbnail is messi's new celebration 🍾 ✨️ 🙌,M6mpXtMm93M,thumbnail is messi s new celebration,neutral,0.0,"['thumbnail messi', 'messi new', 'messi']","[('messi s', 'PERSON')]",3
@VSvimalkumar,2026-06-29T13:09:28Z,0,The One,M6mpXtMm93M,the one,neutral,0.0,[],[],64
@Navvidissajew,2026-06-29T13:07:00Z,9,0:59 wth happened here? Was there a ghost,M6mpXtMm93M,0 59 what the heck happened here was there a ghost,negative,-0.3182,"['59', '59 heck', 'happened ghost']",[],-1
@antonYpauL777,2026-06-29T13:01:04Z,2,"Lionel Messi goal was spectacular,
In between that small gap 😄😜",M6mpXtMm93M,lionel messi goal was spectacular in between that small gap,neutral,0.0,"['messi goal', 'messi', 'lionel messi']","[('lionel messi', 'PERSON')]",-1
@DokoNinjo,2026-06-29T12:59:45Z,1,La famosa parata laser,M6mpXtMm93M,la famosa parata laser,neutral,0.0,"['parata laser', 'famosa parata', 'la famosa']","[('la famosa parata laser', 'ORG')]",4
@Ovimvlog,2026-06-29T12:57:11Z,0,Best messi♥️🇦🇷,M6mpXtMm93M,best messi,positive,0.6369,"['best messi', 'messi', 'best']","[('messi', 'PERSON')]",3
@mostdisciplinedgirl,2026-06-29T12:55:18Z,0,Greatest,M6mpXtMm93M,greatest,positive,0.6369,[],[],36
@NetViro,2026-06-29T12:53:19Z,0,Crazy Bangers Free kick,M6mpXtMm93M,crazy bangers free kick,positive,0.2263,"['free kick', 'bangers free', 'crazy bangers']",[],-1
@TuhinChakraborty-ql4wv,2026-06-29T12:41:54Z,0,❤,M6mpXtMm93M,,neutral,0.0,[],[],0
@iminagy1359,2026-06-29T12:37:44Z,0,"Penalty for Argentina...
